<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Part 2" id="14">
  <quote id="248">
	<id>248</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[The next of Bahá’u’lláh’s Teachings that I would like to present to you is related to the aim of the Bahá’í Faith, which is to unify humanity.  The Bahá’í Teachings we are told that we are the fruits of one tree and the leaves of one branch.  Although we differ from one another physically and emotionally, although we have different talents and capacities, we all bring from the same root; we all belong to the same human family.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="249">
	<id>249</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Humanity can be likened to a vast garden in which grow side by side flowers of every form, color and perfume.  The charm and beauty of the garden lie in this diversity.  We should not allow the differences that exist among us – in our physical characteristics, our temperaments, our backgrounds, our thoughts and opinions – to give rise to conflict and strife.  We should see the members of the human race as beautiful flowers growing in the garden of humanity and rejoice in belonging to this garden.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="250">
	<id>250</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Although the oneness of humankind is an undeniable truth, the peoples of earth are so far from it that unifying them is no easy task.  If you choose to join the Bahá’í community – and it would bring me so much happiness if you would do so – you will participate with the rest of us in our efforts to build and maintain unity.  We are all striving to bring our thoughts and actions in line with our belief in the oneness of humankind.  We are told that, when a thought of war enters our minds, we should immediately replace it with a thought of peace.  When a feeling of hate begins to take shape in our hearts, we should immediately replace it with a feeling of love.  We should do everything possible to overcome our prejudices.  Prejudices of race, color nationality, culture, religion, and sex, these are among the greatest obstacles to building a better work.  So many passages in the Bahá’í writing teach us how to walk in the ways of unity and how to help others take the same path.  There is a wonderful passage from one of the talks of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, of Whom I will speak later, which I have memorized.  He says:]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="251">
	<id>251</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh has drawn the circle of unity, He has made a design for the uniting of all the peoples, and for the gathering of them all under the shelter of the tent of universal unity.  This is the work of the Divine Bounty, and we must all strive with heart and soul until we have the reality of unity in our midst, and as we work, so will strength be given unto us.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Paris Talks, p. 46]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>