<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="1 Corinthians" id="59">
  <quote id="1078">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Wherefore let him that thinketh he standeth take heed lest he fall.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[1 Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[10:12]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1079">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[If I speak in human and angelic tongues but do not have love, I am a resounding gong or a clashing cymbal.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[1 Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[13:1]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1080">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[And if I have the gift of prophesy and comprehend all mysteries and all knowledge; if I have all faith so as to move mountains but do not have love, I am nothing.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[1 Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[13:2]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1081">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[If I give away everything I own, and if I hand my body over so that I may boast but do not have love, I gain nothing.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[1 Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[13:3]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1082">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Love is patient, love is kind. It is not jealous, [love] is not pompous, it is not inflated, it is not rude, it does not seek its own interests, it is not quick-tempered, it does not brood over injury, it does not rejoice over wrongdoing but rejoices with the truth. It bears all things, believes in all things, hopes all things, endures all things.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[1 Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[13:4-7]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1086">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Love never fails. If there are prophecies, they will be brought to nothing; if tounges, they will cease; if knowledge, it will be brought to nothing.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[13:8]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1087">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[For we know partially and we prophesy partially, but when the perfect comes, the partial will pass away.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[13:9-10]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1088">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[When I was a child, I used to talk as a child, think as a child, reason as a child; when I became a man, I put aside childish things. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[13:11]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1089">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[At present, we see indistinctly, as in a mirror, but then face to face. At present I know partially; then I shall know fully, as I am fully known.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[13:12]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1090">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[So faith, hope, love remain, these three; but the greatest of these is love.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[13:13]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1091">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[For I delivered unto you first of all that which I also received, how that Christ died for our sins according to the scriptures; And that he was buried, and that he rose again the third day according to the scriptures: And that he was seen of Cephas, then of the twelve: After that, he was seen of above five hundred brethren at once; of whom the greater part remain unto this present, but some are fallen asleep. After that, he was seen of James; then of all the apostles. And last of all he was seen of me also, as of one born out of due time.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[1 Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[15:3-8]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="1097">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O death, where is thy sting? O grave, where is thy victory?]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[1 Corinthians]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[15:55]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>