<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Albert Einstein" id="190">
  <quote id="6819">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[A happy man is too satisfied with the present to dwell too much on the future.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA["My Future Plans" an essay written at age 17 for school exam (18 September 1896)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6820">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I am by heritage a Jew, by citizenship a Swiss, and by makeup a human being, and only a human being, without any special attachment to any state or national entity whatsoever.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Letter to Alfred Kneser (7 June 1918)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6821">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Try and penetrate with our limited means the secrets of nature and you will find that, behind all the discernible concatenations, there remains something subtle, intangible and inexplicable. Veneration for this force beyond anything that we can comprehend is my religion. To that extent I am, in point of fact, religious.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6822">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance you must keep moving.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Letter to his son Eduard (5 February 1930)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6823">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I believe in intuition and inspiration. Imagination is more important than knowledge. For knowledge is limited, whereas imagination embraces the entire world, stimulating progress, giving birth to evolution. It is, strictly speaking, a real factor in scientific research.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Cosmic Religion : With Other Opinions and Aphorisms (1931)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6824">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Falling in love is not at all the most stupid thing that people do — but gravitation cannot be held responsible for it.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6825">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Our time is distinguished by wonderful achievements in the fields of scientific understanding and the technical application of those insights. Who would not be cheered by this? But let us not forget that human knowledge and skills alone cannot lead humanity to a happy and dignified life. Humanity has every reason to place the proclaimers of high moral standards and values above the discoverers of objective truth. What humanity owes to personalities like Buddha, Moses, and Jesus ranks for me higher than all the achievements of the enquiring and constructive mind. <br/>
What these blessed men have given us we must guard and try to keep alive with all our strength if humanity is not to lose its dignity, the security of its existence, and its joy in living.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Written statement (September 1937)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6826">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Generations to come, it may well be, will scarce believe that such a man as this one ever in flesh and blood walked upon this Earth.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Statement on the occasion of Gandhi's 70th birthday (1939)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6827">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Great spirits have always encountered violent opposition from mediocre minds. The mediocre mind is incapable of understanding the man who refuses to bow blindly to conventional prejudices and chooses instead to express his opinions courageously and honestly.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Letter to Morris Raphael Cohen (19 March 1940)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6828">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Do not worry about your difficulties in Mathematics. I can assure you mine are still greater.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Letter to Barbara Lee Wilson (7 January 1943)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6829">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Journal of France and Germany (1942 - 1944)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6831">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[A new type of thinking is essential if mankind is to survive and move toward higher levels. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Quoted in New York Times (25 May 1946)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6832">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I do not know how the Third World War will be fought, but I can tell you what they will use in the Fourth—rocks!]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Quoted in Liberal Judaism 16 (April-May 1949)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6834">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Science is a wonderful thing if one does not have to earn one's living at it. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Letter to California student E. Holzapfel (March 1951)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6835">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I have no special talents. I am only passionately curious.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Letter to Carl Seelig (11 March 1952)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6836">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[The important thing is not to stop questioning; curiosity has its own reason for existing.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Quoted in LIFE magazine (2 May 1955)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6837">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Try to become not a man of success, but try rather to become a man of value.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Quoted in LIFE magazine (2 May 1955)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6839">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[When a man sits with a pretty girl for an hour, it seems like a minute. But let him sit on a hot stove for a minute and it's longer than any hour. That's relativity.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Quoted in "Expandable Quotable Einstein" (2005)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6840">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I'm not an atheist and I don't think I can call myself a pantheist. We are in the position of a little child entering a huge library filled with books in many different languages. The child knows someone must have written those books. It does not know how. The child dimly suspects a mysterious order in the arrangement of the books but doesn't know what it is. That, it seems to me, is the attitude of even the most intelligent human being toward God. We see a universe marvelously arranged and obeying certain laws, but only dimly understand these laws. Our limited minds cannot grasp the mysterious force that moves the constellations. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[As quoted in Glimpses of the Great (1930) ]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6841">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[My religion consists of an humble admiration for the vast power which manifests itself in that small part of the universe which our poor, weak minds can grasp! ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Wisehart interview (1930?) ]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6842">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[The most beautiful and deepest experience a man can have is the sense of the mysterious. It is the underlying principle of religion as well as all serious endeavor in art and science. He who never had this experience seems to me, if not dead, then at least blind.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[My Credo (1932)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6844">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Even though the realms of religion and science in themselves are clearly marked off from each other, nevertheless there exist between the two strong reciprocal relationships and dependencies.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Science and Religion (1941)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6845">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[...science without religion is lame, religion without science is blind.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Science and Religion (1941)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6846">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[The great moral teachers of humanity were, in a way, artistic geniuses in the art of living.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Religion and Science: Irreconcilable? (1948)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6847">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[While it is true that scientific results are entirely independent from religious or moral considerations, those individuals to whom we owe the great creative achievements of science were all of them imbued with the truly religious conviction that this universe of ours is something perfect and susceptible to the rational striving for knowledge.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Religion and Science: Irreconcilable? (1948)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="6848">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[A man's value to the community depends primarily on how far his feelings, thoughts, and actions are directed towards promoting the good of his fellows. We call him good or bad according to how he stands in this matter.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Albert Einstein]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The World As I See It (1949)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Einstein]]></url>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>