<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Helen Keller" id="168">
  <quote id="5253">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[One can never consent to creep when one feels an impulse to soar.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Address to the American Association to Promote the Teaching of Speech to the Deaf at Mt. Airy, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (8 July 1896)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5254">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I want to say to those who are trying to learn to speak and those who are teaching them: Be of good cheer. Do not think of to-day's failures, but of the success that may come to-morrow. You have set yourselves a difficult task, but you will succeed if you persevere, and you will find a joy in overcoming obstacles — a delight in climbing rugged paths, which you would perhaps never know if you did not sometime slip backward — if the road was always smooth and pleasant. Remember, no effort that we make to attain something beautiful is ever lost. Sometime, somewhere, somehow we shall find that which we seek. We shall speak, yes, and sing, too, as God intended we should speak and sing.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Address to the American Association to Promote the Teaching of Speech to the Deaf (8 July 1896)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5255">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[The only real blind person at Christmas-time is he who has not Christmas in his heart.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA["Christmas in the Dark" in Ladies Home Journal (December 1906)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5256">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[We differ, blind and seeing, one from another, not in our senses, but in the use we make of them, in the imagination and courage with which we seek wisdom beyond the senses.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Five-sensed World (1910)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5257">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[When one door of happiness closes, another opens; but often we look so long at the closed door that we do not see the one which has been opened for us.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[We Bereaved (1929)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5258">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Avoiding danger is no safer in the long run than outright exposure. The fearful are caught as often as the bold.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Let Us Have Faith (1940)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5259">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Life is either a daring adventure, or nothing.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Open Door (1957)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5260">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[The most important day I remember in all my life is the one on which my teacher, Anne Mansfield Sullivan, came to me. I am filled with wonder when I consider the immeasurable contrasts between the two lives which it connects. It was the third of March, 1887, three months before I was seven years old.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Story of My Life (1903), Chapter 3]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5261">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Have you ever been at sea in a dense fog, when it seemed as if a tangible white darkness shut you in, and the great ship, tense and anxious, groped her way toward the shore with plummet and sounding-line, and you waited with beating heart for something to happen? I was like that ship before my education began, only I was without compass or sounding-line, and had no way of knowing how near the harbour was. "Light! give me light!" was the wordless cry of my soul, and the light of love shone on me in that very hour.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Story of My Life (1903), Chapter 3]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5262">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[We walked down the path to the well-house, attracted by the fragrance of the honeysuckle with which it was covered. Some one was drawing water and my teacher placed my hand under the spout. As the cool stream gushed over one hand she spelled into the other the word water, first slowly, then rapidly. I stood still, my whole attention fixed upon the motions of her fingers. Suddenly I felt a misty consciousness as of something forgotten — a thrill of returning thought; and somehow the mystery of language was revealed to me. I knew then that "w-a-t-e-r" meant the wonderful cool something that was flowing over my hand. That living word awakened my soul, gave it light, hope, joy, set it free! There were barriers still, it is true, but barriers that could in time be swept away. <br/>
I left the well-house eager to learn. Everything had a name, and each name gave birth to a new thought. As we returned to the house every object which I touched seemed to quiver with life. That was because I saw everything with the strange, new sight that had come to me. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Story of My Life (1903), Chapter 4]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5263">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[The Bible gives me a deep, comforting sense that "things seen are temporal and things unseen are eternal."]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Story of My Life (1903), Chapter 21]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5264">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[It is curious to observe what different ideals of happiness people cherish, and in what singular places they look for this well-spring of their life. Many look for it in the hoarding of riches, some in the pride of power, and others in the achievements of art and literature; a few seek it in the exploration of their own minds, or in search for knowledge.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5265">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Most people measure their happiness in terms of physical pleasure and material possession. Could they win some visible goal which they have set on the horizon, how happy they could be! Lacking this gift or that circumstance, they would be miserable. If happiness is to be so measured, I who cannot hear or see have every reason to sit in a corner with folded hands and weep. If I am happy in spite of my deprivations, if my happiness is so deep that it is a faith, so thoughtful that it becomes a philosophy of life, — if, in short, I am an optimist, my testimony to the creed of optimism is worth hearing.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5266">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Once I knew the depth where no hope was, and darkness lay on the face of all things. Then love came and set my soul free. Once I knew only darkness and stillness. Now I know hope and joy. Once I fretted and beat myself against the wall that shut me in. Now I rejoice in the consciousness that I can think, act and attain heaven. My life was without past or future; death, the pessimist would say, "a consummation devoutly to be wished." But a little word from the fingers of another fell into my hand that clutched at emptiness, and my heart leaped to the rapture of living. Night fled before the day of thought, and love and joy and hope came up in a passion of obedience to knowledge. Can anyone who escaped such captivity, who has felt the thrill and glory of freedom, be a pessimist?
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5267">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[It is a mistake always to contemplate the good and ignore the evil, because by making people neglectful it lets in disaster. There is a dangerous optimism of ignorance and indifference.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5268">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Although the world is full of suffering, it is full also of the overcoming of it. My optimism, then, does not rest on the absence of evil, but on a glad belief in the preponderance of good and a willing effort always to cooperate with the good, that it may prevail. I try to increase the power God has given me to see the best in everything and every one, and make that Best a part of my life.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5269">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I have found out that though the ways in which I can make myself useful are few, yet the work open to me is endless.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5270">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[To know the history of philosophy is to know that the highest thinkers of the ages, the seers of the tribes and the nations, have been optimists. The growth of philosophy is the story of man's spiritual life.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5271">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[The highest result of education is tolerance. Long ago men fought and died for their faith; but it took ages to teach them the other kind of courage, — the courage to recognize the faiths of their brethren and their rights of conscience. Tolerance is the first principal of community; it is the spirit which conserves the best that all men think.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5272">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[The idea of brotherhood redawns upon the world with a broader significance than the narrow association of members in a sect or creed...]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5273">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[The test of all beliefs is their practical effect in life. If it be true that optimism compels the world forward, and pessimism retards it, then it is dangerous to propagate a pessimistic philosophy.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5274">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Let pessimism once take hold of the mind, and life is all topsy-turvy, all vanity and vexation of spirit. There is no cure for individual or social disorder, except in forgetfulness and annihilation. "Let us eat, drink and be merry," says the pessimist, "for to-morrow we die." If I regarded my life from the point of view of the pessimist, I should be undone. I should seek in vain for the light that does not visit my eyes and the music that does not ring in my ears. I should beg night and day and never be satisfied. I should sit apart in awful solitude, a prey to fear and despair. But since I consider it a duty to myself and to others to be happy, I escape a misery worse than any physical deprivation.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5275">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Who shall dare let his incapacity for hope or goodness cast a shadow upon the courage of those who bear their burdens as if they were privileges?]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5276">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[We have found that our great philosophers and our great men of action are optimists. So, too, our most potent men of letters have been optimists in their books and in their lives. No pessimist ever won an audience commensurately wide with his genius, and many optimistic writers have been read and admired out of all measure to their talents, simply because they wrote of the sunlit side of life.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5277">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Every optimist moves along with progress and hastens it, while every pessimist would keep the worlds at a standstill. The consequence of pessimism in the life of a nation is the same as in the life of the individual. Pessimism kills the instinct that urges men to struggle against poverty, ignorance and crime, and dries up all the fountains of joy in the world.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5278">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement; nothing can be done without hope.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5279">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I believe it is a sacred duty to encourage ourselves and others; to hold the tongue from any unhappy word against God's world, because no man has any right to complain of a universe which God made good, and which thousands of men have striven to keep good. I believe we should so act that we may draw nearer and more near the age when no man shall live at his ease while another suffers. These are the articles of my faith, and there is yet another on which all depends — to bear this faith above every tempest which overfloods it, and to make it a principal in disaster and through affliction. Optimism is the harmony between man's spirit and of God pronouncing His works good.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Optimism (1903)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5280">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Recently I was visited by a very good friend who had just returned from a long walk in the woods, and I asked her what she had observed. “Nothing in particular,” she replied. I might have been incredulous had I not been accustomed to such responses, for long ago I became convinced that the seeing see little. <br/>
How was it possible, I asked myself, to walk for an hour through the woods and see nothing worthy of note? I who cannot see find hundreds of things to interest me through mere touch. I feel the delicate symmetry of a leaf. I pass my hands lovingly about the smooth skin of a silver birch, or the rough, shaggy bark of a pine. In spring I touch the branches of trees hopefully in search of a bud, the first sign of awakening Nature after her winter’s sleep. I feel the delightful, velvety texture of a flower, and discover its remarkable convolutions; and something of the miracle of Nature is revealed to me.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Three Days to See (1933)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5281">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Happiness is the final and perfect fruit of obedience to the laws of life.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Simplest Way to be Happy (1933)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5282">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[A happy life consists not in the absence, but in the mastery of hardships.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Simplest Way to be Happy (1933)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5283">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[It all comes to this: the simplest way to be happy is to do good.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Simplest Way to be Happy (1933)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5284">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[If we spend the time we waste in sighing for the perfect golden fruit in fulfilling the conditions of its growth, happiness will come, must come. It is guaranteed in the very laws of the universe. If it involves some chastening and renunciation, well, the fruit will be all the sweeter for this touch of holiness.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Simplest Way to be Happy (1933)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5285">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Many persons have a wrong idea of what constitutes true happiness. It is not attained through self-gratification but through fidelity to a worthy purpose.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Helen Keller]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Simplest Way to be Happy (1933)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Helen_Keller]]></url>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>