<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<quotes language="english">
	<section name="Ruhi Book 1">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The betterment of the world can be accomplished through pure and goodly deeds, through commendable and seemly conduct.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in The Advent of Divine Justice pp.24-25]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Beware, O people of Bahá, lest ye walk in the ways of them whose words differ from their deeds.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, CXXXIX, p.305]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Son of Being! Bring thyself to account each day ere thou art summoned to a reckoning...]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words  Arabic #31]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Say, O brethren! Let deeds, not words, be your adorning.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words  Persian #5]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Holy words and pure and goodly deeds ascend unto the heaven of celestial glory.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words  Persian #69]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Truthfulness is the foundation of all human virtues.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í World Faith - ‘Abdu'l-Bahá Section, p. 384]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Without truthfulness, progress and success in all the worlds of God are impossible for any soul.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í World Faith - ‘Abdu'l-Bahá Section, p. 384]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Beautify your tongues, O people, with truthfulness, and adorn your souls with the ornament of honesty.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 297]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Let your eye be chaste, your hand faithful, your tongue truthful and your heart enlightened.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 138]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[They who dwell within the tabernacle of God, and are established upon the seats of everlasting glory, will refuse, though they be dying of hunger, to stretch their hands and seize unlawfully the property of their neighbor, however vile and worthless he may be.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 298]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[A kindly tongue is the lodestone of the hearts of men. It is the bread of the spirit, it clotheth the words with meaning, it is the fountain of the light of wisdom and understanding....]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, CXXXII, p. 289]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O ye beloved of the Lord! In this sacred Dispensation, conflict and contention are in no wise permitted. Every aggressor deprives himself of God's grace.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bah World Faith  ‘Abdu'l-Bahá Section, p. 445]]></reference>	
		</quote><quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Nothing whatever can, in this Day, inflict a greater harm upon this Cause than dissension and strife, contention, estrangement and apathy, among the loved ones of God.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, V, p. 9]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Do not be content with showing friendship in words alone, let your heart burn with loving kindness for all who may cross your path.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Paris Talks, p. 16]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[When a thought of war comes, oppose it by a stronger thought of peace. A thought of hatred must be destroyed by a more powerful thought of love.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Paris Talks, p. 29]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[...backbiting quencheth the light of the heart, and extinguisheth the life of the soul.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, CXXV, p.265]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Breathe not the sins of others so long as thou art thyself a sinner.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words  Arabic #27]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Speak no evil, that thou mayest not hear it spoken unto thee, and magnify not the faults of others that thine own faults may not appear great...]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words  Persian #44]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Son of Being! How couldst thou forget thine own faults and busy thyself with the faults of others? Whoso doeth this is accursed of Me.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words  Arabic #26]]></reference>	
		</quote>	
	</section>
	
	<section name="Ruhi Book 2">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O wayfarer in the path of God! Take thou thy portion of the ocean of His grace, and deprive not thyself of the things that lie hidden in its depths. Be thou of them that have partaken of its treasures. A dewdrop out of this ocean would, if shed upon all that are in the heavens and on the earth, suffice to enrich them with the bounty of God, the Almighty, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise. With the hands of renunciation draw forth from its life-giving waters, and sprinkle therewith all created things, that they may be cleansed from all man-made limitations and may approach the mighty seat of God, this hallowed and resplendent Spot.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 279]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O MAN OF TWO VISIONS!  Close one eye and open the other. Close one to the world and all that is therein, and open the other to the hallowed beauty of the Beloved.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Persian Hidden Words #12]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O FRIENDS! Abandon not the everlasting beauty for a beauty that must die, and set not your affections on this mortal world of dust.
]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Persian Hidden Words #14]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O SON OF UTTERANCE! Turn thy face unto Mine and renounce all save Me; for My sovereignty endureth and My dominion perisheth not. If thou seekest another than Me, yea, if thou searchest the universe for evermore, thy quest will be in vain.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Arabic Hidden Words #15]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O BEFRIENDED STRANGER! The candle of thine heart is lighted by the hand of My power, quench it not with the contrary winds of self and passion. The healer of all thine ills is remembrance of Me, forget it not. Make My love thy treasure and cherish it even as thy very sight and life.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Persian Hidden Words #32]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Detachment is as the sun; in whatsoever heart it doth shine it quencheth the fire of covetousness and self.  He whose sight is illumined with the light of understanding will assuredly detach himself from the world and the vanities thereof ....Let not the world and its vileness grieve you.  Happy is he whom riches fill not with vain-glory, nor poverty with sorrow.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in The Bahá'í World]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Gird up the loins of thine endeavor, that haply thou mayest guide thy neighbor to the law of God, the Most Merciful. Such an act, verily, excelleth all other acts in the sight of God, the All-Possessing, the Most High.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 339]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[By the righteousness of God! Whoso openeth his lips in this Day and maketh mention of the name of his Lord, the hosts of Divine inspiration shall descend upon him from the heaven of My name, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 280]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Whoso ariseth to teach Our Cause must needs detach himself from all earthly things, and regard, at all times, the triumph of Our Faith as his supreme objective.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 334]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Be unrestrained as the wind, while carrying the Message of Him Who hath caused the Dawn of Divine Guidance to break.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 339]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[When the victory arriveth, every man shall profess himself as believer and shall hasten to the shelter of God's Faith. Happy are they who in the days of world-encompassing trials have stood fast in the Cause and refused to swerve from its truth.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 319]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O SON OF BEING! Make mention of Me on My earth, that in My heaven I may remember thee, thus shall Mine eyes and thine be solaced.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Arabic Hidden Words #43]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Illumine our hearts, grant us discerning eyes and attentive ears.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 82]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 82]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Grant Thine infinite bestowals, and let the light of Thy guidance shine.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 101]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Unlock the gates of true understanding and let the light of faith shine resplendent.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Promulgation of Universal Peace, p. 116]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Illumine, O Lord, the faces of Thy servants, that they may behold Thee...]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Prayers and Meditations by Bahá’u’lláh, p. 95]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O our Lord! Turn our faces unto Thy merciful countenance...]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 139]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[They who are the beloved of God, in whatever place they gather and whomsoever they may meet, must evince, in their attitude towards God, and in the manner of their celebration of His praise and glory, such humility and submissiveness that every atom of the dust beneath their feet may attest the depth of their devotion. The conversation carried by these holy souls should be informed with such power that these same atoms of dust will be thrilled by its influence. >>
]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 7 (part 1)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[They should conduct themselves in such manner that the earth upon which they tread may never be allowed to address to them such words as these: 'I am to be preferred above you. For witness, how patient I am in bearing the burden which the husbandman layeth upon me. I am the instrument that continually imparteth unto all beings the blessings with which He Who is the Source of all grace hath entrusted me. Notwithstanding the honor conferred upon me, and the unnumbered evidences of my wealth -- a wealth that supplieth the needs of all creation -- behold the measure of my humility, witness with what absolute submissiveness I allow myself to be trodden beneath the feet of men....']]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 7 (part 2)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[My name is ‘Abdu'l-Bahá. My qualification is ‘Abdu'l-Bahá. My reality is ‘Abdu'l-Bahá. My praise is ‘Abdu'l-Bahá. Thraldom to the Blessed Perfection is my glorious and refulgent diadem, and servitude to all the human race my perpetual religion... No name, no title, no mention, no commendation have I, nor will ever have, except ‘Abdu'l-Bahá. This is my longing. This is my greatest yearning. This is my eternal life. This is my everlasting glory.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[quoted in The World Order of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 139]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[All men have been created to carry forward an ever-advancing civilization.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 215]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The Purpose of the one true God, exalted be His glory, in revealing Himself unto men is to lay bare those gems that lie hidden within the mine of their true and inmost selves.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 287]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[God's purpose in sending His Prophets unto men is twofold. The first is to liberate the children of men from the darkness of ignorance, and guide them to the light of true understanding. The second is to ensure the peace and tranquillity of mankind, and provide all the means by which they can be established.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 79]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Men at all times and under all conditions stand in need of one to exhort them, guide them and to instruct and teach them.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 161]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[There can be no doubt whatever that the peoples of the world, of whatever race or religion, derive their inspiration from one heavenly Source, and are the subjects of one God.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 217]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Consort with the followers of all religions in a spirit of friendliness and fellowship.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 22]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The fundamental purpose animating the Faith of God and His Religion is to safeguard the interests and promote the unity of the human race..]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 215]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The religion of God is for love and unity; make it not the cause of enmity or dissension.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 220]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The knowledge of Him, Who is the Origin of all things, and attainment unto Him, are impossible save through knowledge of, and attainment unto, these luminous Beings who proceed from the Sun of Truth.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Kitab-i-Iqan, p. 142]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[No man, however acute his perception, can ever hope to reach the heights which the wisdom and understanding of the Divine Physician have attained.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 80]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The Person of the Manifestation hath ever been the representative and mouthpiece of God. He, in truth, is the Day Spring of God's most excellent Titles, and the Dawning-Place of His exalted Attributes.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 70]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Be ye assured, moreover, that the works and acts of each and every one of these Manifestations of God, nay whatever pertaineth unto them, and whatsoever they may manifest in the future, are all ordained by God, and are a reflection of His Will and Purpose.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 59]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The Eternal Truth is now come. He hath lifted up the Ensign of Power, and is now shedding upon the world the unclouded splendor of His Revelation]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 60]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[He it is Who is the Manifestation of Him Who is the Unknowable, the Invisible of the Invisibles, could ye but perceive it.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 30]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[This is the Day whereon the All-Merciful hath come down in the clouds of knowledge, clothed with manifest sovereignty.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 45]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Every age hath its own problem, and every soul its particular aspiration. The remedy the world needeth in its present-day afflictions can never be the same as that which a subsequent age may require.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 213]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Be anxiously concerned with the needs of the age ye live in, and center your deliberations on its exigencies and requirements.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 213]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[A new life is, in this age, stirring within all the peoples of the earth; and yet none hath discovered its cause or perceived its motive.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 196]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The progress of the world, the development of nations, the tranquillity of peoples, and the peace of all who dwell on earth are among the principles and ordinances of God.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 130]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Religion is, verily, the chief instrument for the establishment of order in the wotrld, and of tranquillity amongst its peoples.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Epistle to the Son of the Wolf, p. 28]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The well-being of mankind, its peace and security, are unattainable unless and until its unity is firmly established.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 286]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The tabernacle of unity hath been raised; regard ye not one another as strangers. Ye are the fruits of one tree, and the leaves of one branch.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 218]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[So powerful is the light of unity that it can illuminate the whole earth.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Epistle to the Son of the Wolf, p. 14]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Set your faces towards unity, and let the radiance of its light shine upon you. Gather ye together, and for the sake of God resolve to root out whatever is the source of contention amongst you.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 217]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[It behoveth man to adhere tenaciously unto that which will promote fellowship, kindliness and unity.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 90]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The light of men is Justice. Quench it not with the contrary winds of oppression and tyranny. The purpose of justice is the appearance of unity among men.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 66]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[No radiance can compare with that of justice. The organization of the world and the tranquillity of mankind depend upon it.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in The Advent of Divine Justice, p. 28]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[That which traineth the world is Justice, for it is upheld by two pillars, reward and punishment. These two pillars are the sources of life to the world.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 27]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Women and men have been and will always be equal in the sight of God.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Compilation of Compilations vol II, p. 379]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Know ye not why We created you all from the same dust? That no one should exalt himself over the other.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Arabic Hidden Words #68]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[In this Day the Hand of divine grace hath removed all distinctions. The servants of God and His handmaidens are regarded on the same plane.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Compilation of Compilations vol II, p. 358]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[It is not desirable that a man be left without knowledge or skills, for he is then but a barren tree.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Education: A Compilation, p. 5]]></reference>	
		</quote>	
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Bend your minds and wills to the education of the peoples and kindreds of the earth...]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 333]]></reference>	
		</quote>	
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Arts, crafts and sciences uplift the world of being, and are conducive to its exaltation. Knowledge is as wings to man's life, and a ladder for his ascent.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Epistle to the Son of the Wolf, p. 26]]></reference>	
		</quote>	
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[In truth, knowledge is a veritable treasure for man, and a source of glory, of bounty, of joy, of exaltation, of cheer and gladness unto him.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Epistle to the Son of the Wolf, p. 27]]></reference>	
		</quote>	
	</section>
	
	<section name="Ruhi Book 3">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Blessed is that teacher who shall arise to instruct the children …]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Bahá’í Education  - A Compilation p.9 (Book 3, p. 7)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
				<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Among the greatest of all services that can possibly be rendered by man to Almighty God is the education and training of children….]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections From The Writings of ‘Abdu’l-Baha #106 p.133 (Book 3, p. 7)]]></reference>	
		</quote>	
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[According to the explicit divine Text, teaching the children is indispensable and obligatory.  It followeth that teachers are servants of the Lord God, since they have arisen to perform this task, which is the same as worship.  You must therefore offer praise with each breath, for you are educating your spiritual children.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá’í Education: A Compilation, p.33 (Book 3, p. 7)]]></reference>	
		</quote>	
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Regard man as a mine rich in gems of inestimable value. Education can, alone, cause it to reveal its treasures, and enable mankind to benefit therefrom.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 260 (Book 3, p. 9)]]></reference>	
		</quote>	
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Whoso ariseth among you to teach the Cause of his Lord, let him, before all else, teach his own self, that his speech may attract the hearts of them that hear him.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh CXXVIII  p. 277 (Book 3, p. 13)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Let God be your fear, O people, and be ye of them that tread the path of righteousness.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh CXXVIII p.275 (Book 3, p. 16)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O God, guide me, protect me, make of me a shining lamp and a brilliant star.  Thou art the Mighty and the Powerful.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá’í Prayers (1985 U.S. Edition) p.37 (Book 3,  p. 37)
]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[So powerful is the light of unity that it can illumine the whole earth.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh CXXXII  p. 288 (Book 3,  p. 38)
]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Son of Spirit!  My first counsel is this:  Possess a pure, kindly and radiant heart …]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Hidden Words, Arabic #1 (Book 3, p. 40)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Tread ye the path of justice, for this, verily, is the straight path.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh CXVIII  p.250 (Book 3, p.43)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[ O Friend!  In the garden of thy heart plant naught but the rose of love …]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Hidden Words, Persian #3 (Book 3, p. 45)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Thou kind Lord! I am a little child, exalt me by admitting me to the kingdom. I am earthly, make me heavenly; I am of the world below, let me belong to the realm above; gloomy, suffer me to become radiant; material, make me spiritual, and grant that I may manifest Thine infinite bounties. Thou art the Powerful, the All-Loving.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 35]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[That one indeed is a man who, today, dedicateth himself to the service of the entire human race.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[leanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh CXVII p.250 (Book 3, p. 47)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Truthfulness is the foundation of all human virtues.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in Shoghi Effendi, The Advent of Divine Justice, 1984 U.S. Edition p.26 (Book 3, p. 49)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Supremely lofty will be thy station, if thou remainest steadfast in the Cause of thy Lord.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh CXV p.246 (Book 3, p. 51)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Son of Man!  Humble thyself before Me, that I may graciously visit thee.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Hidden Words, Arabic #42 (Book 3, p. 54)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Blessed is he who preferreth his brother before himself.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh Revealed after The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, p.71 (Book 3, 56)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[ Beautify your tongues, O people, with truthfulness, and adorn your souls with the ornament of honesty.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh CXXXVI  p. 297 (Book 3, p. 58)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O my Lord!  O my Lord!  I am a child of tender years.  Nourish me from the breast of Thy mercy, train me in the bosom of Thy love, educate me in the school of Thy guidance and develop me under the shadow of Thy bounty.  Deliver me from darkness, make me a brilliant light; free me from unhappiness, make me a flower of the rose garden; suffer me to become a servant of Thy threshold and confer upon me the disposition and nature of the righteous; make me a cause of bounty to the human world and crown my head with the diadem of eternal life.  Verily, Thou art the Powerful, the Mighty, the Seer, the Hearer.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá’í Prayers pp.37/38 (Book 3, p. 60)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[To give and be generous are attributes of Mine; well it is with him that adorneth himself with My virtues.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Hidden Words, Persian #49 (Book 3, p. 61)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Blessed is he who mingleth with all men in a spirit of utmost kindliness and love.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh CLVI p334 (Book 3, p. 63)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The sign of love is fortitude under My decree and patience under My trials.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Hidden Words, Arabic, #48 (Book 3, p. 65)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Son of Being!  My love is My stronghold; he that entereth therein is safe and secure, and he that turneth away shall surely stray and perish.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Hidden Words, Arabic #9 (Book 3, p. 68)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Put your trust in God, and commit your affairs to His keeping.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in Shoghi Effendi,The Advent of Divine Justice,1984 U.S. Edition p.82 (Book 3, p. 71)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
	</section>
	<section name="Ruhi Book 4">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[There is no time to lose. There is no room left for vacillation. Multitudes hunger for the Bread of Life. The stage is set. The firm and irrevocable Promise is given. God's own Plan has been set in motion .... The powers of heaven and earth mysteriously assist in its execution .... Let the doubter arise and himself verify the truth of such assertions. To try, to persevere, is to ensure ultimate and complete victory.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Shoghi Effendi]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Messages to America: Selected Letters and Cablegrams Addressed to the Bahá’ís of North America, 1932 - 1946, p. 17]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Beseech almighty Providence that He may graciously enable you to attain, in that capital, the seat of true sovereignty, and to enter the mansion of the Beloved.  A secret lies hidden in that city.  When made manifest, it shall turn the earth into paradise.  My hope is that you may partake of its grace and recognize its splendor.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[citied in The Dawnbreakers, pp. 85-86]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Is there any Remover of difficulties save God? Say: Praised be God! He is God! All are His servants, and all abide by His bidding!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá’í Prayers, p. 27]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Say: God sufficeth all things above all things, and nothing in the heavens or in the earth but God sufficeth. Verily, He is in Himself the Knower, the Sustainer, the Omnipotent.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá’í Prayers, p. 28]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O My beloved friends! You are the bearers of the name of God in this Day. You have been chosen as the repositories of His mystery. It behoves each one of you to manifest the attributes of God, and to exemplify by your deeds and words the signs of His righteousness, His power and glory. The very members of your body must bear witness to the loftiness of your purpose, the integrity of your life, the reality of your faith, and the exalted character of your devotion. >> ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Address to the Letters of the Living, The Dawn-Breakers, pp. 92-94 (part 1)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> For verily I say, this is the Day spoken of by God in His Book: 'On that day will We set a seal upon their mouths yet shall their hands speak unto Us, and their feet shall bear witness to that which they shall have done.' Ponder the words of Jesus addressed to His disciples, as He sent them forth to propagate the Cause of God. In words such as these, He bade them arise and fulfil their mission: >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Address to the Letters of the Living, The Dawn-Breakers, pp. 92-94 (part 2)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> 'Ye are even as the fire which in the darkness of the night has been kindled upon the mountain-top. Let your light shine before the eyes of men. Such must be the purity of your character and the degree of your renunciation, that the people of the earth may through you recognize and be drawn closer to the heavenly Father who is the Source of purity and grace. For none has seen the Father who is in heaven. You who are His spiritual children must by your deeds exemplify His virtues, and witness to His glory. You are the salt of the earth, but if the salt have lost its savour, wherewith shall it be salted? >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Address to the Letters of the Living, The Dawn-Breakers, pp. 92-94 (part 3)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> Such must be the degree of your detachment, that into whatever city you enter to proclaim and teach the Cause of God, you should in no wise expect either meat or reward from its people. Nay, when you depart out of that city, you should shake the dust from off your feet. As you have entered it pure and undefiled, so must you depart from that city. For verily I say, the heavenly Father is ever with you and keeps watch over you. If you be faithful to Him, He will assuredly deliver into your hands all the treasures of the earth, and will exalt you above all the rulers and kings of the world.' >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Address to the Letters of the Living, The Dawn-Breakers, pp. 92-94 (part 4)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> O My Letters! Verily I say, immensely exalted is this Day above the days of the Apostles of old. Nay, immeasurable is the difference! You are the witnesses of the Dawn of the promised Day of God. You are the partakers of the mystic chalice of His Revelation. Gird up the loins of endeavour, and be mindful of the words of God as revealed in His Book: 'Lo, the Lord thy God is come, and with Him is the company of His angels arrayed before Him!' Purge your hearts of worldly desires, and let angelic virtues be your adorning. Strive that by your deeds you may bear witness to the truth of these words of God, and beware lest, by 'turning back,' He may 'change you for another people,' who 'shall not be your like,' and who shall take from you the Kingdom of God. >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Address to the Letters of the Living, The Dawn-Breakers, pp. 92-94 (part 4)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> The days when idle worship was deemed sufficient are ended. The time is come when naught but the purest motive, supported by deeds of stainless purity, can ascend to the throne of the Most High and be acceptable unto Him. 'The good word riseth up unto Him, and the righteous deed will cause it to be exalted before Him.' You are the lowly, of whom God has thus spoken in His Book: ‘And We desire to show favour to those who were brought low in the land, and to make them spiritual leaders among men, and to make them Our heirs.' >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Address to the Letters of the Living, The Dawn-Breakers, pp. 92-94 (part 6)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> You have been called to this station; you will attain to it, only if you arise to trample beneath your feet every earthly desire, and endeavour to become those 'honoured servants of His who speak not till He hath spoken, and who do His bidding.' You are the first Letters that have been generated from the Primal Point, the first Springs that have welled out from the Source of this Revelation. Beseech the Lord your God to grant that no earthly entanglements, no worldly affections, no ephemeral pursuits, may tarnish the purity, or embitter the sweetness, of that grace which flows through you. >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Address to the Letters of the Living, The Dawn-Breakers, pp. 92-94 (part 7)
]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> I am preparing you for the advent of a mighty Day. Exert your utmost endeavour that, in the world to come, I, who am now instructing you, may, before the mercy-seat of  God, rejoice in your deeds and glory in your achievements. The secret of the Day that is to come is now concealed. It can neither be divulged nor estimated. The newly born Bábe of that Day excels the wisest and most venerable men of this time, and the lowliest and most unlearned of that period shall surpass in understanding the most erudite and accomplished divines of this age. Scatter throughout the length and breadth of this land, and, with steadfast feet and sanctified hearts, prepare the way for His coming. Heed not your weaknesses and frailty; fix your gaze upon the invincible power of the Lord, your God, the Almighty. >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Address to the Letters of the Living, The Dawn-Breakers, pp. 92-94 (part 8)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> Has He not, in past days, caused Abraham, in spite of His seeming helplessness, to triumph over the forces of Nimrod? Has He not enabled Moses, whose staff was His only companion, to vanquish Pharaoh and his hosts? Has He not established the ascendancy of Jesus, poor and lowly as He was in the eyes of men, over the combined forces of the Jewish people? Has He not subjected the barbarous and militant tribes of Arabia to the holy and transforming discipline of Muhammad, His Prophet? Arise in His name, put your trust wholly in Him, and be assured of ultimate victory.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Address to the Letters of the Living, The Dawn-Breakers, pp. 92-94 (part 9)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[No man shall attain the shores of the ocean of true understanding except he be detached from all that is in heaven and on earth. Sanctify your souls, O ye peoples of the world, that haply ye may attain that station which God hath destined for you and enter thus the tabernacle which, according to the dispensations of Providence, hath been raised in the firmament of the Bayan.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ The Kitab-i-Iqan, p. 3]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[This is that which hath descended from the realm of glory, uttered by the tongue of power and might, and revealed unto the Prophets of old. We have taken the inner essence thereof and clothed it in the garment of brevity, as a token of grace unto the righteous, that they may stand faithful unto the Covenant of God, may fulfill in their lives His trust, and in the realm of spirit obtain the gem of Divine virtue.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ The Hidden Words, p. 3]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The first duty prescribed by God for His servants is the recognition of Him Who is the Dayspring of His Revelation and the Fountain of His laws, Who representeth the Godhead in both the Kingdom of His Cause and the world of creation. Whoso achieveth this duty hath attained unto all good; and whoso is deprived thereof hath gone astray, though he be the author of every righteous deed. It behooveth every one who reacheth this most sublime station, this summit of transcendent glory, to observe every ordinance of Him Who is the Desire of the world. These twin duties are inseparable. Neither is acceptable without the other.  Thus hath it been decreed by Him Who is the Source of Divine inspiration. >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, pp. 21-23 (part 1)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> They whom God hath endued with insight will readily recognize that the precepts laid down by God constitute the highest means for the maintenance of order in the world and the security of its peoples. He that turneth away from them is accounted among the abject and foolish. We, verily, have commanded you to refuse the dictates of your evil passions and corrupt desires, and not to transgress the bounds which the Pen of the Most High hath fixed, for these are the breath of life unto all created things. The seas of Divine wisdom and Divine utterance have risen under the breath of the breeze of the All-Merciful. Hasten to drink your fill, O men of understanding! They that have violated the Covenant of God by breaking His commandments, and have turned back on their heels, these have erred grievously in the sight of God, the All-Possessing, the Most High. >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, pp. 21-23 (part 2)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> O ye peoples of the world! Know assuredly that My commandments are the lamps of My loving providence among My servants, and the keys of My mercy for My creatures. Thus hath it been sent down from the heaven of the Will of your Lord, the Lord of Revelation. Were any man to taste the sweetness of the words which the lips of the All-Merciful have willed to utter, he would, though the treasures of the earth be in his possession, renounce them one and all, that he might vindicate the truth of even one of His commandments, shining above the Dayspring of His bountiful care and loving-kindness. >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, pp. 21-23 (part 3)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> Say: From My laws the sweet-smelling savour of My garment can be smelled, and by their aid the standards of Victory will be planted upon the highest peaks. The Tongue of My power hath, from the heaven of My omnipotent glory, addressed to My creation these words: Observe My commandments, for the love of My beauty. Happy is the lover that hath inhaled the divine fragrance of his Best-Beloved from these words, laden with the perfume of a grace which no tongue can describe. By My life! He who hath drunk the choice wine of fairness from the hands of My bountiful favour will circle around My commandments that shine above the Dayspring of My creation. >>]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, pp. 21-23 (part 4)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[>> Think not that We have revealed unto you a mere code of laws. Nay, rather, We have unsealed the choice Wine with the fingers of might and power. To this beareth witness that which the Pen of Revelation hath revealed. Meditate upon this, O men of insight!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, pp. 21-23 (part 5)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
	</section>
	
	
	<section name="Ruhi Book 6">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O thou lamp who art enkindled with the fire of the Love of God! Verily, I read thy recent letter which showed thy strong love, thy being ablaze with the fire of the love of thy Lord, the Mighty, the Praised, and the penetration of the Spirit of Truth in thy limbs, nerves, veins, arteries, bones, blood and flesh, until it hath taken the reins of power from thy hands and moveth thee as it willeth, causeth thee to speak in what it willeth and attracteth thee as it willeth. This is becoming of whatever heart is replenished with the spirit of the love of God. Thou shalt surely behold wondrous traces and shalt discover the signs of thy Mighty Lord.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá vol 3, pp. 716-717 (Book 6, p. 11)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Say: To assist Me is to teach My Cause. This is a theme with which whole Tablets are laden. This is the changeless commandment of God, eternal in the past, eternal in the future.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 196, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Be not dismayed, O peoples of the world, when the day star of My beauty is set, and the heaven of My tabernacle is concealed from your eyes. Arise to further My Cause, and to exalt My Word amongst men. We are with you at all times, and shall strengthen you through the power of truth.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, p. 34, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The Pen of the Most High hath decreed and imposed upon every one the obligation to teach this Cause.... God will, no doubt, inspire whosoever detacheth himself from all else but Him, and will cause the pure waters of wisdom and utterance to gush out and flow copiously from his heart.    ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 314, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[God hath prescribed unto every one the duty of teaching His Cause. Whoever ariseth to discharge this duty, must needs, ere he proclaimeth His Message, adorn himself with the ornament of an upright and praiseworthy character, so that his words may attract the hearts of such as are receptive to his call.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 335, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O ye beloved of God! Repose not yourselves on your couches, nay bestir yourselves as soon as ye recognize your Lord, the Creator, and hear of the things which have befallen Him, and hasten to His assistance. Unloose your tongues, and proclaim unceasingly His Cause. This shall be better for you than all the treasures of the past and of the future, if ye be of them that comprehend this truth.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 330, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[If one teaches one whom he loves because of his love for him, then he will not teach one whom he loves not; and that is not of God.  If one teaches in order to derive the promised benefit to himself, this too is not from God.   If he teaches because of God's Will that God may be known -- and for that reason only -- he will receive knowledge and wisdom, and his words will have effect -- being made powerful by the Holy Spirit -- and will take root in the souls of those who are in the right condition to receive them.  In such a case the benefit to the teacher in growth is as ninety percent compared to the ten percent of gain to the hearer, because he becomes like a tree bearing fruit through the power of God.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in Star of the West, vol III, no. 19 (2 March 1913) p. 1, (Book 6 p. 18)
]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[This is the day in which to speak. It is incumbent upon the people of Baha to strive, with the utmost patience and forbearance, to guide the peoples of the world to the Most Great Horizon. Every body calleth aloud for a soul. Heavenly souls must needs quicken, with the breath of the Word of God, the dead bodies with a fresh spirit.     
]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in The Advent of Divine Justice, pp. 82-83, (Book 6 p. 28)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O thou son of the Kingdom! All things are beneficial if joined with the love of God; and without His love all things are harmful, and act as a veil between man and the Lord of the Kingdom. When His love is there, every bitterness turneth sweet, and every bounty rendereth a wholesome pleasure. For example, a melody, sweet to the ear, bringeth the very spirit of life to a heart in love with God, yet staineth with lust a soul engrossed in sensual desires. And every branch of learning, conjoined with the love of God, is approved and worthy of praise; but bereft of His love, learning is barren -- indeed, it bringeth on madness. Every kind of knowledge, every science, is as a tree: if the fruit of it be the love of God, then is it a blessed tree, but if not, that tree is but dried-up wood, and shall only feed the fire.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, p. 190, (Book 6 p. 34)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[By the righteousness of God! Whoso openeth his lips in this Day and maketh mention of the name of his Lord, the hosts of Divine inspiration shall descend upon him from the heaven of My name, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise. On him shall also descend the Concourse on high, each bearing aloft a chalice of pure light. Thus hath it been foreordained in the realm of God's Revelation, by the behest of Him Who is the All-Glorious, the Most Powerful.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 280, (Book 6 p. 34)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[They that have forsaken their country for the purpose of teaching Our Cause -- these shall the Faithful Spirit strengthen through its power. A company of Our chosen angels shall go forth with them, as bidden by Him Who is the Almighty, the All-Wise. How great the blessedness that awaiteth him that hath attained the honor of serving the Almighty!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 334, (Book 6 pp. 34/35)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[He, verily, will aid everyone that aideth Him, and will remember everyone that remembereth Him. To this beareth witness this Tablet that hath shed the splendor of the loving-kindness of your Lord, the All-Glorious, the All-Compelling.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in The Advent of Divine Justice, p. 76, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Say: Beware, O people of Baha, lest the strong ones of the earth rob you of your strength, or they who rule the world fill you with fear. Put your trust in God, and commit your affairs to His keeping. He, verily, will, through the power of truth, render you victorious, and He, verily, is powerful to do what He willeth, and in His grasp are the reins of omnipotent might.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in The Advent of Divine Justice p. 82, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[By God besides Whom is none other God! Should any one arise for the triumph of our Cause, him will God render victorious though tens of thousands of enemies be leagued against him. And if his love for Me wax stronger, God will establish his ascendancy over all the powers of earth and heaven. Thus have We breathed the spirit of power into all regions.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[cited in The World Order of Bahá’u’lláh: Selected Letters, p.106, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[He will come to your aid with invisible hosts, and support you with armies of inspiration from the Concourse above; He will send unto you sweet perfumes from the highest Paradise, and waft over you the pure breathings that blow from the rose gardens of the Company on high. He will breathe into your hearts the spirit of life, cause you to enter the Ark of salvation, and reveal unto you His clear tokens and signs. Verily is this abounding grace. Verily is this the victory that none can deny.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, no. 157, p. 196, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O ye servants of the Sacred Threshold! The triumphant hosts of the Celestial Concourse, arrayed and marshaled in the Realms above, stand ready and expectant to assist and assure victory to that valiant horseman who with confidence spurs on his charger into the arena of service. Well is it with that fearless warrior, who armed with the power of true Knowledge, hastens unto the field, disperses the armies of ignorance, and scatters the hosts of error, who holds aloft the Standard of Divine Guidance, and sounds the Clarion of Victory. By the righteousness of the Lord! He hath achieved a glorious triumph and obtained the true victory.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, no. 208, pp. 276-77, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Let us too bear in mind the example which our beloved Master has clearly set before us. Wise and tactful in His approach, wakeful and attentive in His early intercourse, broad and liberal in all His public utterances, cautious and gradual in the unfolding of the essential verities of the Cause, passionate in His appeal yet sober in argument, confident in tone, unswerving in conviction, dignified in His manners -- such were the distinguishing features of our Beloved's noble presentation of the Cause of Bahá’u’lláh.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Shoghi Effendi]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá’í Administration:  Selected Messages, pp. 69-70, (Book 6 p. 70)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[As for you, O ye lovers of God, make firm your steps in His Cause, with such resolve that ye shall not be shaken though the direst of calamities assail the world. By nothing, under no conditions, be ye perturbed. Be ye anchored fast as the high mountains, be stars that dawn over the horizon of life, be bright lamps in the gatherings of unity, be souls humble and lowly in the presence of the friends, be innocent in heart. Be ye symbols of guidance and lights of godliness, severed from the world, clinging to the handhold that is sure and strong, spreading abroad the spirit of life, riding the Ark of salvation. Be ye daysprings of generosity, dawning-points of the mysteries of existence, sites where inspiration alighteth, rising-places of splendours, souls that are sustained by the Holy Spirit, enamoured of the Lord, detached from all save Him, holy above the characteristics of humankind, clothed in the attributes of the angels of heaven, that ye may win for yourselves the highest bestowal of all, in this new time, this wondrous age.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, no. 199, p. 253, (Book 6 p. 73)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The opportunities which the turmoil of the present age presents, with all the sorrows which it evokes, the fears which it excites, the disillusionment which it produces, the perplexities which it creates, the indignation which it arouses, the revolt which it provokes, the grievances it engenders, the spirit of restless search which it awakens, must, in like manner, be exploited for the purpose of spreading far and wide, the knowledge of the redemptive power of the Faith of Bahá’u’lláh, and for enlisting fresh recruits in the ever-swelling army of His followers. So precious an opportunity, so rare a conjunction of favorable circumstances, may never again recur.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Shoghi Effendi]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Advent of Divine Justice, p. 48, (Book 6 p. 87)]]></reference>	
		</quote>
	</section>


	<section name="Anna's Presentation Part 1">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[From our previous conversations, you know that the Bahá’í Faith is a world religion whose purpose is to unite all the races and peoples in one universal Cause and one common Faith.  Bahá’ís are the followers of Bahá’u’lláh, Who they believe is the Promised One of all Ages.  As you know, the traditions of all most every people include the promise of a future when peace and harmony will be established on earth and humankind will live in prosperity.  We believe that the promised hour has come and that Bahá’u’lláh is the great Personage Whose Teachings will enable humanity to build a new world. In one of His Writings, Bahá’u’lláh says:]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[That which the Lord hath ordained as the sovereign remedy and mightiest instrument for the healing of all the world is the union of all its peoples in one universal Cause, one common Faith.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá'u'lláh, p. 255]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[If it is all right with you, the first of Bahá’u’lláh’s Teachings I will describe for you is about God and our relationship with Him.  Bahá’u’lláh teaches us that God is unknowable in His Essence.  This means that we should not make images of God in our mind, thinking of Him, for example, as a man.  In general, that whish has been created cannot understand its creator.  For instance, a table cannot understand the nature of the carpenter who made it.  The carpenter’s existence is totally incomprehensible to the objects he makes.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[God is the Creator of all things.  He has made the heavens and earth, with its mountains and valleys, its deserts and seas, its rivers, its meadows and trees.  God has created and animals and God has created the human being.  The reason behind our creation, we are told by Bahá’u’lláh, is love.  He says:]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Son of Man! I loved thy creation, hence I created thee.  Wherefore, do thou love Me, that I may name thy name and fill thy soul with the spirit of life.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh,]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words, Arabic no. 4, p. 4]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[So although God’s existence is far beyond our understanding, His love touches our lives and our beings ceaselessly.  The way this love flows to us is through His Eternal Covenant.  According to this Eternal Covenant, God never leaves us alone and without guidance.  Whenever humanity moves away from Him and forgets His Teachings, a Manifestation of God appears and makes His Will and Purpose known to us.  ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The word “manifest” means to reveal, to bring forth something that was not known before.  The Manifestations of God are those special Beings Who reveal to humanity the Word and the Will of God; thus when we listen to Them, we are responding to the Call of God.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[There is an example from the physical world that helps us to understand the concept of “Manifestation” as taught by Bahá’u’lláh.  In this world, the sun is the source of all warmth and light, without which life would not exist on the planet.  Yet the sun itself does not descend to earth, and if we tried to approach it, we would be totally consumed.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[But suppose we take a well-polished mirror and point it towards the sun.  In it we will see the image of the sun, and the more perfectly polished the mirror, the more perfect the image will be.  The Manifestations of God are like perfect Mirrors that reflect the Light of God in all its Splendor.  And all these Mirrors reflect the same Light.  While God is beyond our reach, these perfect Beings come to us from time to time, live among us, give us guidance, and fill us with the energy we need to progress, materially and spiritually.
]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>		
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[You are fortunate to have been raised according to the Teachings sent by God to humanity some two thousand years ago through His Manifestation, Christ, Whose Station is that of the Son of God.  Now you can receive the Teachings of a new Manifestation, Bahá’u’lláh, Whose title means the Glory of God, Bahá’u’lláh’s Teachings, then, are in perfect harmony with the Teachings of Christ, but they address the condition of humanity today.  If you think for a moment about the plight of humanity, I am sure you will agree that the time is right for another Manifestation of God to have appeared.  Let me recite for you a passage from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh that speaks about the Day in which we live:
]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[This is the Day in which God's most excellent favors have been poured out upon men, the Day in which His most mighty grace hath been infused into all created things. It is incumbent upon all the peoples of the world to reconcile their differences, and, with perfect unity and peace, abide beneath the shadow of the Tree of His care and loving-kindness.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá'u'lláh, p. 6]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Before going on, perhaps I should stop here so that we can discuss any questions you have.  What do you think about what I have said up to now?]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
</section>
<section name="Anna's Presentation Part 2">		
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The next of Bahá’u’lláh’s Teachings that I would like to present to you is related to the aim of the Bahá’í Faith, which is to unify humanity.  The Bahá’í Teachings we are told that we are the fruits of one tree and the leaves of one branch.  Although we differ from one another physically and emotionally, although we have different talents and capacities, we all bring from the same root; we all belong to the same human family.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Humanity can be likened to a vast garden in which grow side by side flowers of every form, color and perfume.  The charm and beauty of the garden lie in this diversity.  We should not allow the differences that exist among us – in our physical characteristics, our temperaments, our backgrounds, our thoughts and opinions – to give rise to conflict and strife.  We should see the members of the human race as beautiful flowers growing in the garden of humanity and rejoice in belonging to this garden.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Although the oneness of humankind is an undeniable truth, the peoples of earth are so far from it that unifying them is no easy task.  If you choose to join the Bahá’í community – and it would bring me so much happiness if you would do so – you will participate with the rest of us in our efforts to build and maintain unity.  We are all striving to bring our thoughts and actions in line with our belief in the oneness of humankind.  We are told that, when a thought of war enters our minds, we should immediately replace it with a thought of peace.  When a feeling of hate begins to take shape in our hearts, we should immediately replace it with a feeling of love.  We should do everything possible to overcome our prejudices.  Prejudices of race, color nationality, culture, religion, and sex, these are among the greatest obstacles to building a better work.  So many passages in the Bahá’í writing teach us how to walk in the ways of unity and how to help others take the same path.  There is a wonderful passage from one of the talks of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, of Whom I will speak later, which I have memorized.  He says:]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh has drawn the circle of unity, He has made a design for the uniting of all the peoples, and for the gathering of them all under the shelter of the tent of universal unity.  This is the work of the Divine Bounty, and we must all strive with heart and soul until we have the reality of unity in our midst, and as we work, so will strength be given unto us.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Paris Talks, p. 46]]></reference>	
		</quote>

</section>
<section name="Anna's Presentation Part 3">		
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh was born in 1817 in Tihrán, the capital of Iran.  From His early childhood, He showed signs of greatness.  He received some instruction at home, but did not need to attend school, for He was endowed by God with innate knowledge.  Bahá’u’lláh came from a noble family and when he was a young man, was offered a high position in the court of the King, but He refused it.  He wished to dedicate His time to helping the oppressed, the sick and the poor, and to champion the cause of justice.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[There are two aspects of Bahá’u’lláh’s life which I would like to mention in particular.  One is the suffering He endured.  The other is the tremendous influence He had on the hearts and minds of people.  These actually characterize the lives of all the Manifestations of God.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh’s sufferings began the moment He arose to proclaim the Cause of God.  His life was one of exile, imprisonment and persecution.  He was put in chains in a dark and dismal dungeon in Tihrán.  He was exiled four times from land to land, finally being sent to the Prison City of ‘Akká in the Ottoman Empire.  So intense were His sufferings there that He has referred to Akká as the “Most Great Prison”.  In one of His Tablets, we read:]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Remember My days during thy days, and My distress and banishment in this remote prison. And be thou so steadfast in My love that thy heart shall not waver, even if the swords of the enemies rain blows upon thee and all the heavens and the earth arise against thee.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 211]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[I always carry in my bag a small notebook in which I write my favorite passages from the Bahá’í writings.  Let me read for you what Bahá’u’lláh has said about His sufferings:]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>		
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The Ancient Beauty hath consented to be bound with chains that mankind may be released from its bondage, and hath accepted to be made a prisoner within this most mighty Stronghold that the whole world may attain unto true liberty. He hath drained to its dregs the cup of sorrow, that all the peoples of the earth may attain unto abiding joy, and be filled with gladness. This is of the mercy of your Lord, the Compassionate, the Most Merciful. We have accepted to be abased, O believers in the Unity of God, that ye may be exalted, and have suffered manifold afflictions, that ye might prosper and flourish. He Who hath come to build anew the whole world, behold, how they that have joined partners with God have forced Him to dwell within the most desolate of cities!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá'u'lláh, pp. 99-100]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Every effort was made by two powerful courts – those of the King of Iran and the Ottoman Emperor – to oppose Bahá’u’lláh and His Teachings.  But the Light of Truth is not easily extinguished.  The very water that is poured on this fire to put out its flame turns into oil, and the fire burns with more intensity.  Nothing could be done to stop Bahá’u’lláh’s growing influence.  The farther the authorities banished Him, the greater the number of people who were attracted to His Teachings and recognized His Power and Majesty.  In spite of constant persecution, Bahá’u’lláh continued to reveal the Word of God for more than forty years and brought so much love and spiritual energy into this world that the final victory of His Cause is certain.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh passed away in 1892.  His Shrine, which we consider the Holiest Spot on earth, is located near the city of ‘Akká.  Here are some postcards I have of the entrance to the Shrine and the gardens surrounding it.  You don’t know how much I would like to go on pilgrimage to the Holy Land.  I hope, someday, you will be able to do so as well.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>

</section>
<section name="Anna's Presentation Part 4">		
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Several years before Bahá’u’lláh proclaimed His Mission, God sent a special Messenger to announce His coming.  This great Messenger took the title “The Báb” which means the gate.  He was indeed a gate to the knowledge of God and to a new era in human existence.  For six years He taught ceaselessly that the appearance of the new Manifestation of God was near and prepared the way for His coming.  He told the people that they were witnessing the dawn of a new Age, the dawn of the Promised Day of God.  He called upon them to purify their hearts from earthly vanities so that they could recognize Him Whom God would soon manifest.	]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Thousands upon thousands of people accepted the Message of the Báb and began to follow His Teachings.  But the government of Iran and the powerful clergy who ruled over the masses rose against Him.  His followers were persecuted and large numbers were put to death.  The Báb Himself at the age of 31 was martyred by a regiment of soldiers who, at the orders of the government, suspended Him in a public square and opened fire on Him. So that you can see how penetrating the Words of the Báb are, I would like to recite to you two of His prayers:]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Is there any Remover of difficulties save God? Say: Praised be God! He is God! All are His servants, and all abide by His bidding!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 28]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Say: God sufficeth all things above all things, and nothing in the heavens or in the earth but God sufficeth. Verily, He is in Himself the Knower, the Sustainer, the Omnipotent.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 29]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Many Bahá’ís know especially the first prayer by heart and say it either aloud or mentally in times of difficulties.  If you want, we can pause a little and you can memorize it.  It is really easy to do so.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>		
</section>
<section name="Anna's Presentation Part 5">		
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The idea most central to our lives as Bahá’ís is that we have entered into a Covenant with Bahá’u’lláh.  As you know, in all other religions, after the passing of the Manifestation, His followers had thousands of disputes among themselves and, as a result, split the religion into many sects.  The cause of disunity was sometimes the desire for leadership of certain ambitious individuals.  But, when differences of opinion arose between even sincere believers about what the Words of the Manifestation meant, no one had been authorized by the Manifestation Himself to settle the disagreements, and this contributed to conflict and dissension.  Each set of interpretations led to the creation of a different sect.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh has protected His Faith against such division by endowing it with a unique power, the power of the Covenant.  Before His passing, He stated in the clearest terms, in writing, that after Him, all Bahá’ís should turn to 'Abdu'l-Bahá.  'Abdu'l-Bahá, His oldest Son, was thus named the sole Interpreter of His Words and the Center of His Covenant.  He had been raised by Bahá’u’lláh Himself, had recognized His Station even as a child, and had shared the sufferings of His Father.  He was a most precious gift given to humanity, the perfect Exemplar of all Bahá’í Teachings.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA['Abdu'l-Bahá lived on this earth for 77 years.  He was born on the same night the Báb declared His Mission in 1844 and passed away in November 1921.  His life was filled with affliction, but to everyone who entered His presence He brought the greatest joy and happiness.  After the passing of His Father, the responsibility for the Bahá’í community fell on His shoulders, and He labored day and night to spread the Faith throughout the East and the West.  We wrote thousands of Tablets to individuals and groups everywhere and clarified the Teachings of His Father.  His interpretations are now an essential part of the Writings of the Bahá’í Faith.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[By focusing on 'Abdu'l-Bahá as the Center of Bahá’u’lláh’s Covenant, the Bahá’ís of the world remain united in their efforts to live a Bahá’í life and to create a new civilization.  We remember that as part of our promise to Bahá’u’lláh, we are to love one another and, in 'Abdu'l-Bahá, we see the perfect example of one who loves.  We remember that we must uphold justice, that we must be generous, that we must overlook the faults of others, and from the example of 'Abdu'l-Bahá we learn justice, generosity and forgiveness.  More than anything else, by keeping our focus on 'Abdu'l-Bahá, we are always aware of our covenant with Bahá’u’lláh that we will not allow the unity of His followers to be broken and that, united as a worldwide community, we will labor until the oneness of humankind has been firmly established.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[In His Will and Testament, 'Abdu'l-Bahá has named His grandson the Guardian of the Faith and after His passing, Shoghi Effendi became the authorized interpreter of the Teachings.  For 36 years, he continued the work of His Grandfather, clarifying the Words of the Manifestation and firmly establishing His Faith in all parts of the planet.  Five and half years after his passing, the Bahá’ís of the world elected the Universal House of Justice, as envisioned by Bahá’u’lláh and clearly described by 'Abdu'l-Bahá and the Guardian.  The Universal House of Justice is the supreme institution of the Faith to which all the Bahá’ís of the world now turn.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>		
</section>
<section name="Anna's Presentation Part 6">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Many of the ideas I have explained on this last subject require a great deal of thought.  If you agree, some other time we can discuss this matter in more depth.  For that discussion, I will bring a few passages from Bahá’u’lláh’s Book of the Covenant as well as the Will and Testament of 'Abdu'l-Bahá so we can read them together.  But let me go on and present to you a few other ideas you will want to know about the Bahá’í Faith right from the beginning.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[A most important aspect of every religion is the laws that the Manifestation brings to humanity in order to guide it in the right path.  Some of these laws and commandments are eternal, others changes as humanity progresses and evolves.  In the Faith we are taught that we should not think of Bahá’í laws as a series of do’s and don’ts.  Bahá’u’lláh tells us that His laws are ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[A most important aspect of every religion is the laws that the Manifestation brings to humanity in order to guide it in the right path.  Some of these laws and commandments are eternal, others changes as humanity progresses and evolves.  In the Faith we are taught that we should not think of Bahá’í laws as a series of do’s and don’ts.  Bahá’u’lláh tells us that His laws are "...the lamps of My loving providence among My servants, and the keys of My mercy for My creatures." (Bahá'u'lláh, The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, p. 22) Nor should we obey these laws out of fear of punishment, for He clearly has stated in His Most Holy Book:  “Observe My commandments, for the love of My beauty."(Bahá'u'lláh, The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, p. 22)]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[These ideas will become clearer if I give you a few examples of Bahá’í laws.  In the physical world, human beings have to eat every day.  This is a requirement of the human body; if we don’t, we will get sick and quickly die.  We can say, then, that eating daily is a law of physical existence which has to be obeyed.  In the same way one of the commandments of Bahá’u’lláh is that we should pray every day.  Like our body, our soul needs constant nourishment, and prayer provides the nourishment for our spiritual growth.  There are many beautiful prayers revealed by the Báb, By Bahá’u’lláh and by 'Abdu'l-Bahá which we can say when we are alone or recite in meetings.  Some of these prayers are special, and some are obligatory.  One obligatory prayer is recited by Bahá’ís every day sometime between noon and sunset.  It says:]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[I bear witness, O my God, that Thou hast created me to know Thee and to worship Thee. I testify, at this moment, to my powerlessness and to Thy might, to my poverty and to Thy wealth. There is none other God but Thee, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 4]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[It is a short and beautiful prayer and having seen how easy it is for you to memorize verses, I am sure you will know it by heart after repeating it a few times.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>		
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[In another commandment, Bahá’u’lláh prohibits backbiting and calumny.  This is important because, if you think about it, one of the greatest enemies of unity is backbiting.  And unfortunately, it has become an established practice among most of humanity to talk about other people’s faults in their absence.  Everybody seems to be concerned with everybody else’s shortcomings, which are made bigger and bigger as they are constantly mentioned.  'Abdu'l-Bahá tells us to do just the opposite.  If we see ten good qualities in someone and one fault, we should concentrate on the ten, and even if a person has ten faults and only one good quality we should focus on that one quality.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Companion of My Throne!  Hear no evil, and see no evil, abase not thyself, neither sigh and weep.  Speak no evil, that thou mayest not hear it spoken unto thee, and magnify not the faults of others that thine own faults may not appear great; and wish not the abasement of anyone, that thine own abasement be not exposed.  Live then the days of thy life, that are less than a fleeting moment, with thy mind stainless, thy heart unsullied, thy thoughts pure, and thy nature sanctified, so that, free and content, thou mayest put away this mortal frame, and repair unto the mystic paradise and abide in the eternal kingdom forevermore.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words, Persian no. 44, p. 37]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Although this does not affect us much at our age, you should also know that Bahá’u’lláh prohibits the drinking of alcohol and, of course, substance abuse.  Drinking alcohol is really one of the greatest social ills that exists today in the world.  It is one of the most common causes of violence and the ruin of healthy family life.  To tell you the truth, I have never understood why people would take something that interferes with their minds and makes them lose their ability to think clearly.  Drinking makes people capable of acting in shameful ways, when we have actually been created noble.  I know a beautiful quote from Bahá’u’lláh’s Writings about nobility:]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Son of Spirit!  I created thee rich, why dost thou bring thyself down to poverty? Noble I made thee, wherewith dost thou abase thyself?  Out of the essence of knowledge I gave thee being, why seekest thou enlightenment from anyone beside Me?  Out of the clay of love I molded thee, how dost thou busy thyself with another? Turn thy sight unto thyself, that thou mayest find Me standing within thee, mighty, powerful and self-subsisting.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words, Arabic no. 13, pp. 6-7]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Another commandment of Bahá’u’lláh, which is one of my favorites, is about the obligation of parents and society to educate children.  Here, I have in my notebook a short passage from 'Abdu'l-Bahá’s Writings that explains this well:]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Therefore, the beloved of God and the maid-servants of the Merciful must train their children with life and heart and teach them in the school of virtue and perfection.  They must not be lax in this matter; they must not be inefficient.  Truly, if a babe did not live at all it were better than to let it grow ignorant, for that innocent babe, in later life, would become afflicted with innumerable defects, responsible to and questioned by God, reproached and rejected by the people.  What a sin this would be and what an omission!    The first duty of the beloved of God and the maid-servants of the Merciful is this: They must strive by all possible means to educate both sexes, male and female; girls like boys; there is no difference whatsoever between them.  The ignorance of both is blameworthy, and negligence in both cases is reprovable.  'Are they who know and they who do not know equal?']]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá Abbas, vol. 3, pp. 579-580]]></reference>	
		</quote>		
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[You know, after I reflected on this great commandment, I decided to do something about it.  So I hold a Bahá’í children’s class with a friend once every week and we have seventeen students.  I would love to invite you to come and help us with our class. Do you have time this Saturday afternoon?]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>

</section>

<section name="Anna's Presentation Part 7">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[I am sure you are aware that I am inviting you to join a religion and not just accept a collection of nice ideals.  In fact, the Bahá’í Faith is a very organized religion whose aim is nothing less than the unification of the entire human race.  It will be helpful for you to think of the work of the Bahá’ís as the building of a world civilization.  The Universal House of Justice tells us that there are three participants in this work, each with a very important role.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The first participant is the individual believer.  It is the duty of this individual to remain firm in the Covenant, to strive daily to bring his or her life in line with Bahá’u’lláh’s Teachings, and to serve humanity, always conscious of the fact that life does not end with death and that one’s relation with God is eternal.  After death, our souls become free and continue to progress towards God for all eternity.  Our lives here are very much like the life of an infant in the womb of the mother.  For some nine months the child develops faculties – eyes, ears, hands and so on – to be used later in this world.  In the same way, we are to develop here the spiritual faculties that we need to progress in the other worlds of God.  Of course, we do not achieve our purpose by just thinking about it.  We have to work, serve our fellow human beings, and share the knowledge we gain with others.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The second participant is the community.  Human beings were not created to exist alone.  We live in communities and must work together to build the new civilization.  The community closest to us is the local one which consists of the Bahá’ís of our village or town.  It is in the local community where we learn to cooperate with one another, to grow together and become united.  In addition to being members of the local community, we are also members of the national community and then the worldwide Bahá’í community which is constantly expanding and attracting people from every religious background, race, and nationality.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[The institutions of the Faith, the Universal House of Justice tells us, represent the third participant in the building of the new civilization.  This is a subject about which we will have to talk some more when we discuss the Covenant.  For now, let me just mention that included in the commandments of Bahá’u’lláh are many related to the way society should be organized.  In the past, the Manifestations of God have not said much about how their followers should organize themselves and people have had to discover how to do this by themselves.  But in the case of the Bahá’í Faith, Bahá’u’lláh has brought His own Administrative Order, which means that He has told us what institutions we must create, how they should function, and how humanity should be governed.  ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[We have already spoken about the supreme institution, which is the Universal House of Justice.  In each country, Bahá’ís elect once a year the National Spiritual Assembly, and in each locality, the Local Spiritual Assembly.  This is the institution that you will get to know the soonest.  There are no priests or clergy in the Bahá’í Faith, and it is the Local Spiritual Assembly that guides the affairs of the community and watches over the well-being of the individual believers.  A Local Spiritual Assembly consists of nine members elected in a prayerful atmosphere by secret ballot by all the adult believers in the community.  Spiritual Assemblies are extremely important to Bahá’ís.  Through them we learn how human affairs are to be administered and how a new order can be established in society, an order which is to be known as the World Order of Bahá’u’lláh.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O God! Refresh and gladden my spirit. Purify my heart. Illumine my powers. I lay all my affairs in Thy hand. Thou art my Guide and my Refuge. I will no longer be sorrowful and grieved; I will be a happy and joyful being. O God! I will no longer be full of anxiety, nor will I let trouble harass me. I will not dwell on the unpleasant things of life.  O God! Thou art more friend to me than I am to myself. I dedicate myself to Thee, O Lord. ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 152]]></reference>	
		</quote>		
</section>

	<section name="Ruhi Book 7">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O My servants! Were ye to discover the hidden, the shoreless oceans of My incorruptible wealth, ye would, of a certainty, esteem as nothing the world, nay, the entire creation.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 323]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[He is the Compassionate, the All-Bountiful! O God, my God! Thou seest me, Thou knowest me; Thou art my Haven and my Refuge. None have I sought nor any will I seek save Thee; no path have I trodden nor any will I tread but the path of Thy love. In the darksome night of despair, my eye turneth expectant and full of hope to the morn of Thy boundless favour and at the hour of dawn my drooping soul is refreshed and strengthened in remembrance of Thy beauty and perfection. He whom the grace of Thy mercy aideth, though he be but a drop, shall become the boundless ocean, and the merest atom which the outpouring of Thy loving-kindness assisteth, shall shine even as the radiant star. Shelter under Thy protection, O Thou Spirit of purity, Thou Who art the All-Bountiful Provider, this enthralled, enkindled servant of Thine. Aid him in this world of being to remain steadfast and firm in Thy love and grant that this broken-winged bird attain a refuge and shelter in Thy divine nest that abideth upon the celestial tree.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 30]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Thus I exhort each of you, realizing its power and beauty, to sacrifice all your thoughts, words and actions to bring the knowledge of the Love of God into every heart.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Paris Talks, p. 81]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[… ye must in this matter -- that is, the serving of humankind -- lay down your very lives, and as ye yield yourselves, rejoice.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 72]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[If only thou couldst know what a high station is destined for those souls who are severed from the world, are powerfully attracted to the Faith, and are teaching, under the sheltering shadow of Bahá'u'lláh! How thou wouldst rejoice, how thou wouldst, in exultation and rapture, spread thy wings and soar heavenward -- for being a follower of such a way, and a traveller toward such a Kingdom.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 100
]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Hold ye fast to the hem of God's garment, and direct all your efforts toward furthering His Covenant, and burning ever more brightly with the fire of His love, that your hearts may leap for joy in the breathings of servitude which well out from the breast of 'Abdu'l-Bahá.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 85]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Let us put aside all thoughts of self; let us close our eyes to all on earth, let us neither make known our sufferings nor complain of our wrongs. Rather let us become oblivious of our own selves, and drinking down the wine of heavenly grace, let us cry out our joy, and lose ourselves in the beauty of the All-Glorious.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 236]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Ye are the angels, if your feet be firm, your spirits rejoiced, your secret thoughts pure, your eyes consoled, your ears opened, your breasts dilated with joy, and your souls gladdened, and if you arise to assist the Covenant, to resist dissension and to be attracted to the Effulgence!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í World Faith, p. 359]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[At all times do I speak of you and call you to mind. I pray unto the Lord, and with tears I implore Him to rain down all these blessings upon you, and gladden your hearts, and make blissful your souls, and grant you exceeding joy and heavenly delights....]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 37]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[My only joy in this swiftly-passing world was to tread the stony path of God and to endure hard tests and all material griefs. For  otherwise, this earthly life would prove barren and vain, and better would be death. The tree of being would produce no fruit; the sown field of this existence would yield no harvest. Thus it is my hope that once again some circumstance will make my cup of anguish to brim over, and that beauteous Love, that Slayer of souls, will dazzle the beholders again. Then will this heart be blissful, this soul be blessed.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 226]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Then rose the Sun of Truth and the splendours of the Kingdom were shed over east and west. Those who had eyes to see rejoiced at the glad tidings and cried out: 'O blessed, blessed are we!', and they witnessed the inner reality of all things, and uncovered the mysteries of the Kingdom. Delivered then from their fancies and their doubts, they beheld the light of truth, and so exhilarated did they become from draining the chalice of God's love, that they utterly forgot the world and their own selves. Dancing for joy they hastened to the place of their own martyrdom and there, where men die for love, they flung away their heads and hearts.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 33]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O God, O Thou Who hast cast Thy splendour over the luminous realities of men, shedding upon them the resplendent lights of knowledge and guidance, and hast chosen them out of all created things for this supernal grace, and hast caused them to encompass all things, to understand their inmost essence, and to disclose their mysteries, bringing them forth out of darkness into the visible world! "He verily showeth His special mercy to whomsoever He will. O Lord, help Thou Thy loved ones to acquire knowledge and the sciences and arts, and to unravel the secrets that are treasured up in the inmost reality of all created beings. Make them to hear the hidden truths that are written and embedded in the heart of all that is. Make them to be ensigns of guidance amongst all creatures, and piercing rays of the mind shedding forth their light in this, the "first life". Make them to be leaders unto Thee, guides unto Thy path, runners urging men on to Thy Kingdom. Thou verily art the Powerful, the Protector, the Potent, the Defender, the Mighty, the Most Generous.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[ The Compilation of Compilations vol. I, p. 251]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Apart from these provisions Bahá'u'lláh exhorts His followers to consort, with amity and concord and without discrimination, with  the adherents of all religions; warns them to guard against fanaticism, sedition, pride, dispute and contention; inculcates upon them immaculate cleanliness, strict truthfulness, spotless chastity, trustworthiness; hospitality, fidelity, courtesy, forbearance, justice and fairness; counsels them to be "even as the fingers of one hand and the limbs of one body"; calls upon them to arise and serve His Cause; and assures them of His undoubted aid.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Shoghi Effendi]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[God Passes By, p. 214]]></reference>	
		</quote>
	</section>
<section name="Prayers">
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Blessed is the spot, and the house, and the place, and the city, and the heart, and the mountain, and the refuge, and the cave, and the valley, and the land, and the sea, and the island, and the meadow where mention of God hath been made, and His praise glorified.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[My God, my Adored One, my King, my Desire! What tongue can voice my thanks to Thee? I was heedless, Thou didst awaken me. I had turned back from Thee, Thou didst graciously aid me to turn towards Thee. I was as one dead, Thou didst quicken me with the water of life. I was withered, Thou didst revive me with the heavenly stream of Thine utterance which hath flowed forth from the Pen of the All-Merciful.<br/> O Divine Providence! All existence is begotten by Thy bounty; deprive it not of the waters of Thy generosity, neither do Thou withhold it from the ocean of Thy mercy. I beseech Thee to aid and assist me at all times and under all conditions, and seek from the heaven of Thy grace Thine ancient favor. Thou art, in truth, the Lord of bounty, and the Sovereign of the kingdom of eternity.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[ Lord! Pitiful are we, grant us Thy favor; poor, bestow upon us a share from the ocean of Thy wealth; needy, do Thou satisfy us; abased, give us Thy glory. The fowls of the air and the beasts of the field receive their meat each day from Thee, and all beings partake of Thy care and loving-kindness.<br/> Deprive not this feeble one of Thy wondrous grace and vouchsafe by Thy might unto this helpless soul Thy bounty.<br/> Give us our daily bread, and grant Thine increase in the necessities of life, that we may be dependent on none other but Thee, may commune wholly with Thee, may walk in Thy ways and declare Thy mysteries. Thou art the Almighty and the Loving and the Provider of all mankind. ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Say: God sufficeth all things above all things, and nothing in the heavens or in the earth but God sufficeth. Verily, He is in Himself the Knower, the Sustainer, the Omnipotent.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[I adjure Thee by Thy might, O my God! Let no harm beset me in times of tests, and in moments of heedlessness guide my steps aright through Thine inspiration. Thou art God, potent art Thou to do what Thou desirest. No one can withstand Thy Will or thwart Thy Purpose.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[ O God! Educate these children. These children are the plants of Thine orchard, the flowers of Thy meadow, the roses of Thy garden. Let Thy rain fall upon them; let the Sun of Reality shine upon them with Thy love. Let Thy breeze refresh them in order that they may be trained, grow and develop, and appear in the utmost beauty. Thou art the Giver. Thou art the Compassionate.
]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA['Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[I beg Thee to forgive me, O my Lord, for every mention but the mention of Thee, and for every praise but the praise of Thee, and for every delight but delight in Thy nearness, and for every pleasure but the pleasure of communion with Thee, and for every joy but the joy of Thy love and of Thy good-pleasure, and for all things pertaining unto me which bear no relationship unto Thee, O Thou Who art the Lord of lords, He Who provideth the means and unlocketh the doors.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Thy name is my healing, O my God, and remembrance of Thee is my remedy. Nearness to Thee is my hope, and love for Thee is my companion. Thy mercy to me is my healing and my succor in both this world and the world to come. Thou, verily, art the All-Bountiful, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[I have wakened in Thy shelter, O my God, and it becometh him that seeketh that shelter to abide within the Sanctuary of Thy protection and the Stronghold of Thy defense. Illumine my inner being, O my Lord, with the splendors of the Dayspring of Thy Revelation, even as Thou didst illumine my outer being with the morning light of Thy favor.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Create in me a pure heart, O my God, and renew a tranquil conscience within me, O my Hope! Through the spirit of power confirm Thou me in Thy Cause, O my Best-Beloved, and by the light of Thy glory reveal unto me Thy path, O Thou the Goal of my desire! Through the power of Thy transcendent might lift me up unto the heaven of Thy holiness, O Source of my being, and by the breezes of Thine eternity gladden me, O Thou Who art my God! Let Thine everlasting melodies breathe tranquillity on me, O my Companion, and let the riches of Thine ancient countenance deliver me from all except Thee, O my Master, and let the tidings of the revelation of Thine incorruptible Essence bring me joy, O Thou Who art the most manifest of the manifest and the most hidden of the hidden!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O my Lord! Make Thy beauty to be my food, and Thy presence my drink, and Thy pleasure my hope, and praise of Thee my action, and remembrance of Thee my companion, and the power of Thy sovereignty my succorer, and Thy habitation my home, and my dwelling-place the seat Thou hast sanctified from the limitations imposed upon them who are shut out as by a veil from Thee.<br/> Thou art, verily, the Almighty, the All-Glorious, the Most Powerful.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O God! Refresh and gladden my spirit. Purify my heart. Illumine my powers. I lay all my affairs in Thy hand. Thou art my Guide and my Refuge. I will no longer be sorrowful and grieved; I will be a happy and joyful being. O God! I will no longer be full of anxiety, nor will I let trouble harass me. I will not dwell on the unpleasant things of life.<br/> O God! Thou art more friend to me than I am to myself. I dedicate myself to Thee, O Lord.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Lord my God! Assist Thy loved ones to be firm in Thy Faith, to walk in Thy ways, to be steadfast in Thy Cause. Give them Thy grace to withstand the onslaught of self and passion, to follow the light of divine guidance. Thou art the Powerful, the Gracious, the Self-Subsisting, the Bestower, the Compassionate, the Almighty, the All-Bountiful.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O my God! O my God! Unite the hearts of Thy servants, and reveal to them Thy great purpose. May they follow Thy commandments and abide in Thy law. Help them, O God, in their endeavor, and grant them strength to serve Thee. O God! Leave them not to themselves, but guide their steps by the light of Thy knowledge, and cheer their hearts by Thy love. Verily, Thou art their Helper and their Lord.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>	
		</quote>

	</section>




<section name="Long Obligatory Prayer">

		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Thou Who art the Lord of all names and the Maker of the heavens! I beseech Thee by them Who are the Daysprings of Thine invisible Essence, the Most Exalted, the All-Glorious, to make of my prayer a fire that will burn away the veils which have shut me out from Thy beauty, and a light that will lead me unto the ocean of Thy Presence.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Whoso wisheth to recite this prayer, let him stand up and turn unto God, and, as he standeth in his place, let him gaze to the right and to the left, as if awaiting the mercy of his Lord, the Most Merciful, the Compassionate. Then let him say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Thou the Desire of the world and the Beloved of the nations! Thou seest me turning toward Thee, and rid of all attachment to anyone save Thee, and clinging to Thy cord, through whose movement the whole creation hath been stirred up. I am Thy servant, O my Lord, and the son of Thy servant. Behold me standing ready to do Thy will and Thy desire, and wishing naught else except Thy good pleasure. I implore Thee by the Ocean of Thy mercy and the Daystar of Thy grace to do with Thy servant as Thou willest and pleasest. By Thy might which is far above all mention and praise! Whatsoever is revealed by Thee is the desire of my heart and the beloved of my soul. O God, my God! Look not upon my hopes and my doings, nay rather look upon Thy will that hath encompassed the heavens and the earth. By Thy Most Great Name, O Thou Lord of all nations! I have desired only what Thou didst desire, and love only what Thou dost love.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then raise his hands in supplication toward God—blessed and exalted be He—and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Exalted art Thou above the description of anyone save Thyself, and the comprehension of aught else except Thee. ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then kneel, and bowing his forehead to the ground, let him say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Make my prayer, O my Lord, a fountain of living waters whereby I may live as long as Thy sovereignty endureth, and may make mention of Thee in every world of Thy worlds.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then stand and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Thou in separation from Whom hearts and souls have melted, and by the fire of Whose love the whole world hath been set aflame! I implore Thee by Thy Name through which Thou hast subdued the whole creation, not to withhold from me that which is with Thee, O Thou Who rulest over all men! Thou seest, O my Lord, this stranger hastening to his most exalted home beneath the canopy of Thy majesty and within the precincts of Thy mercy; and this transgressor seeking the ocean of Thy forgiveness; and this lowly one the court of Thy glory; and this poor creature the orient of Thy wealth. Thine is the authority to command whatsoever Thou willest. I bear witness that Thou art to be praised in Thy doings, and to be obeyed in Thy behests, and to remain unconstrained in Thy bidding.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him again raise his hands in supplication, and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Thou seest, O my God, how my spirit hath been stirred up within my limbs and members, in its longing to worship Thee, and in its yearning to remember Thee and extol Thee; how it testifieth to that whereunto the Tongue of Thy Commandment hath testified in the kingdom of Thine utterance and the heaven of Thy knowledge. I love, in this state, O my Lord, to beg of Thee all that is with Thee, that I may demonstrate my poverty, and magnify Thy bounty and Thy riches, and may declare my powerlessness, and manifest Thy power and Thy might. ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then raise his hands, and repeat three times the Greatest Name. Let him then bend down with hands resting on the knees before God—blessed and exalted be He—and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[There is no God but Thee, the Almighty, the All-Bountiful. There is no God but Thee, the Ordainer, both in the beginning and in the end. O God, my God! Thy forgiveness hath emboldened me, and Thy mercy hath strengthened me, and Thy call hath awakened me, and Thy grace hath raised me up and led me unto Thee. Who, otherwise, am I that I should dare to stand at the gate of the city of Thy nearness, or set my face toward the lights that are shining from the heaven of Thy will? Thou seest, O my Lord, this wretched creature knocking at the door of Thy grace, and this evanescent soul seeking the river of everlasting life from the hands of Thy bounty. Thine is the command at all times, O Thou Who art the Lord of all names; and mine is resignation and willing submission to Thy will, O Creator of the heavens!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then stand and raise his hands twice in supplication, and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Greater is God than every great one!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then raise his hands thrice, and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Too high art Thou for the praise of those who are nigh unto Thee to ascend unto the heaven of Thy nearness, or for the birds of the hearts of them who are devoted to Thee to attain to the door of Thy gate. I testify that Thou hast been sanctified above all attributes and holy above all names. No God is there but Thee, the Most Exalted, the All-Glorious. ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then kneel and, bowing his forehead to the ground, say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[I testify unto that whereunto have testified all created things, and the Concourse on high, and the inmates of the all-highest Paradise, and beyond them the Tongue of Grandeur itself from the all-glorious Horizon, that Thou art God, that there is no God but Thee, and that He Who hath been manifested is the Hidden Mystery, the Treasured Symbol, through Whom the letters B and E (Be) have been joined and knit together. I testify that it is He Whose name hath been set down by the Pen of the Most High, and Who hath been mentioned in the Books of God, the Lord of the Throne on high and of earth below.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then seat himself and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O Lord of all being and Possessor of all things visible and invisible! Thou dost perceive my tears and the sighs I utter, and hearest my groaning, and my wailing, and the lamentation of my heart. By Thy might! My trespasses have kept me back from drawing nigh unto Thee; and my sins have held me far from the court of Thy holiness. Thy love, O my Lord, hath enriched me, and separation from Thee hath destroyed me, and remoteness from Thee hath consumed me. I entreat Thee by Thy footsteps in this wilderness, and by the words “Here am I. Here am I” which Thy chosen Ones have uttered in this immensity, and by the breaths of Thy Revelation, and the gentle winds of the Dawn of Thy Manifestation, to ordain that I may gaze on Thy beauty and observe whatsoever is in Thy Book. ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then stand erect and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Praise be to Thee, O my God, that Thou hast aided me to remember Thee and to praise Thee, and hast made known unto me Him Who is the Dayspring of Thy signs, and hast caused me to bow down before Thy Lordship, and humble myself before Thy Godhead, and to acknowledge that which hath been uttered by the Tongue of Thy grandeur.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then repeat the Greatest Name thrice, and bend down with hands resting on the knees, and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[O God, my God! My back is bowed by the burden of my sins, and my heedlessness hath destroyed me. Whenever I ponder my evil doings and Thy benevolence, my heart melteth within me, and my blood boileth in my veins. By Thy Beauty, O Thou the Desire of the world! I blush to lift up my face to Thee, and my longing hands are ashamed to stretch forth toward the heaven of Thy bounty. Thou seest, O my God, how my tears prevent me from remembering Thee and from extolling Thy virtues, O Thou the Lord of the Throne on high and of earth below! I implore Thee by the signs of Thy Kingdom and the mysteries of Thy Dominion to do with Thy loved ones as becometh Thy bounty, O Lord of all being, and is worthy of Thy grace, O King of the seen and the unseen!]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then rise and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[Praise be unto Thee, O our God, that Thou hast sent down unto us that which draweth us nigh unto Thee, and supplieth us with every good thing sent down by Thee in Thy Books and Thy Scriptures. Protect us, we beseech Thee, O my Lord, from the hosts of idle fancies and vain imaginations. Thou, in truth, art the Mighty, the All-Knowing.]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then repeat the Greatest Name thrice, and kneel with his forehead to the ground, and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<text><![CDATA[I testify, O my God, to that whereunto Thy chosen Ones have testified, and acknowledge that which the inmates of the all-highest Paradise and those who have circled round Thy mighty Throne have acknowledged. The kingdoms of earth and heaven are Thine, O Lord of the worlds! ]]></text>
			<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
			<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
			<introtext><![CDATA[Let him then raise his head, and seat himself, and say:]]></introtext>	
		</quote>
	</section>

</quotes>


