<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Part 1" id="13">
  <quote id="236">
	<id>236</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[From our previous conversations, you know that the Bahá’í Faith is a world religion whose purpose is to unite all the races and peoples in one universal Cause and one common Faith.  Bahá’ís are the followers of Bahá’u’lláh, Who they believe is the Promised One of all Ages.  As you know, the traditions of all most every people include the promise of a future when peace and harmony will be established on earth and humankind will live in prosperity.  We believe that the promised hour has come and that Bahá’u’lláh is the great Personage Whose Teachings will enable humanity to build a new world. In one of His Writings, Bahá’u’lláh says:]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="237">
	<id>237</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[That which the Lord hath ordained as the sovereign remedy and mightiest instrument for the healing of all the world is the union of all its peoples in one universal Cause, one common Faith.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá'u'lláh, p. 255]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="238">
	<id>238</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[If it is all right with you, the first of Bahá’u’lláh’s Teachings I will describe for you is about God and our relationship with Him.  Bahá’u’lláh teaches us that God is unknowable in His Essence.  This means that we should not make images of God in our mind, thinking of Him, for example, as a man.  In general, that wish has been created cannot understand its creator.  For instance, a table cannot understand the nature of the carpenter who made it.  The carpenter’s existence is totally incomprehensible to the objects he makes.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="239">
	<id>239</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[God is the Creator of all things.  He has made the heavens and earth, with its mountains and valleys, its deserts and seas, its rivers, its meadows and trees.  God has created and animals and God has created the human being.  The reason behind our creation, we are told by Bahá’u’lláh, is love.  He says:]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="240">
	<id>240</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O Son of Man! I loved thy creation, hence I created thee.  Wherefore, do thou love Me, that I may name thy name and fill thy soul with the spirit of life.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh,]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Hidden Words, Arabic no. 4, p. 4]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="241">
	<id>241</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[So although God’s existence is far beyond our understanding, His love touches our lives and our beings ceaselessly.  The way this love flows to us is through His Eternal Covenant.  According to this Eternal Covenant, God never leaves us alone and without guidance.  Whenever humanity moves away from Him and forgets His Teachings, a Manifestation of God appears and makes His Will and Purpose known to us.  ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="242">
	<id>242</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[The word “manifest” means to reveal, to bring forth something that was not known before.  The Manifestations of God are those special Beings Who reveal to humanity the Word and the Will of God; thus when we listen to Them, we are responding to the Call of God.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="243">
	<id>243</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[There is an example from the physical world that helps us to understand the concept of “Manifestation” as taught by Bahá’u’lláh.  In this world, the sun is the source of all warmth and light, without which life would not exist on the planet.  Yet the sun itself does not descend to earth, and if we tried to approach it, we would be totally consumed.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="244">
	<id>244</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[But suppose we take a well-polished mirror and point it towards the sun.  In it we will see the image of the sun, and the more perfectly polished the mirror, the more perfect the image will be.  The Manifestations of God are like perfect Mirrors that reflect the Light of God in all its Splendor.  And all these Mirrors reflect the same Light.  While God is beyond our reach, these perfect Beings come to us from time to time, live among us, give us guidance, and fill us with the energy we need to progress, materially and spiritually.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="245">
	<id>245</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[You are fortunate to have been raised according to the Teachings sent by God to humanity some two thousand years ago through His Manifestation, Christ, Whose Station is that of the Son of God.  Now you can receive the Teachings of a new Manifestation, Bahá’u’lláh, Whose title means the Glory of God, Bahá’u’lláh’s Teachings, then, are in perfect harmony with the Teachings of Christ, but they address the condition of humanity today.  If you think for a moment about the plight of humanity, I am sure you will agree that the time is right for another Manifestation of God to have appeared.  Let me recite for you a passage from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh that speaks about the Day in which we live:
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="246">
	<id>246</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[This is the Day in which God's most excellent favors have been poured out upon men, the Day in which His most mighty grace hath been infused into all created things. It is incumbent upon all the peoples of the world to reconcile their differences, and, with perfect unity and peace, abide beneath the shadow of the Tree of His care and loving-kindness.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá'u'lláh, p. 6]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="247">
	<id>247</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Before going on, perhaps I should stop here so that we can discuss any questions you have.  What do you think about what I have said up to now?]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>