<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Part 4" id="16">
  <quote id="260">
	<id>260</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Several years before Bahá’u’lláh proclaimed His Mission, God sent a special Messenger to announce His coming.  This great Messenger took the title “The Báb” which means the gate.  He was indeed a gate to the knowledge of God and to a new era in human existence.  For six years He taught ceaselessly that the appearance of the new Manifestation of God was near and prepared the way for His coming.  He told the people that they were witnessing the dawn of a new Age, the dawn of the Promised Day of God.  He called upon them to purify their hearts from earthly vanities so that they could recognize Him Whom God would soon manifest.	]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="261">
	<id>261</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Thousands upon thousands of people accepted the Message of the Báb and began to follow His Teachings.  But the government of Iran and the powerful clergy who ruled over the masses rose against Him.  His followers were persecuted and large numbers were put to death.  The Báb Himself at the age of 31 was martyred by a regiment of soldiers who, at the orders of the government, suspended Him in a public square and opened fire on Him. So that you can see how penetrating the Words of the Báb are, I would like to recite to you two of His prayers:]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="262">
	<id>262</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Is there any Remover of difficulties save God? Say: Praised be God! He is God! All are His servants, and all abide by His bidding!]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 28]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="263">
	<id>263</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Say: God sufficeth all things above all things, and nothing in the heavens or in the earth but God sufficeth. Verily, He is in Himself the Knower, the Sustainer, the Omnipotent.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 29]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="264">
	<id>264</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Many Bahá’ís know especially the first prayer by heart and say it either aloud or mentally in times of difficulties.  If you want, we can pause a little and you can memorize it.  It is really easy to do so.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>