<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Medium Obligatory Prayer" id="154">
  <quote id="5105">
    <introtext><![CDATA[TO BE RECITED DAILY, IN THE MORNING, AT NOON, AND IN THE EVENING: Whoso wisheth to pray, let him wash his hands, and while he washeth, let him say:]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Strengthen my hand, O my God, that it may take hold of Thy Book with such steadfastness that the hosts of the world shall have no power over it. Guard it, then, from meddling with whatsoever doth not belong unto it. Thou art, verily, the Almighty, the Most Powerful.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Medium Obligatory Prayer, paragraph 1]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5106">
    <introtext><![CDATA[And while washing his face, let him say:]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I have turned my face unto Thee, O my Lord! Illumine it with the light of Thy countenance. Protect it, then, from turning to anyone but Thee.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Medium Obligatory Prayer, paragraph 2]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5107">
    <introtext><![CDATA[Then let him stand up, and facing the Qiblih (Point of Adoration, i.e. Bahjí, ‘Akká), let him say:]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[God testifieth that there is none other God but Him. His are the kingdoms of Revelation and of creation. He, in truth, hath manifested Him Who is the Dayspring of Revelation, Who conversed on Sinai, through Whom the Supreme Horizon hath been made to shine, and the Lote-Tree beyond which there is no passing hath spoken, and through Whom the call hath been proclaimed unto all who are in heaven and on earth: “Lo, the All-Possessing is come. Earth and heaven, glory and dominion are God’s, the Lord of all men, and the Possessor of the Throne on high and of earth below!”]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Medium Obligatory Prayer, paragraph 3]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5108">
    <introtext><![CDATA[Let him, then, bend down, with hands resting on the knees, and say:]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Exalted art Thou above my praise and the praise of anyone beside me, above my description and the description of all who are in heaven and all who are on earth!]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Medium Obligatory Prayer, paragraph 4]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5109">
    <introtext><![CDATA[Then, standing with open hands, palms upward toward the face, let him say:]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Disappoint not, O my God, him that hath, with beseeching fingers, clung to the hem of Thy mercy and Thy grace, O Thou Who of those who show mercy art the Most Merciful!]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Medium Obligatory Prayer, paragraph 5]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5110">
    <introtext><![CDATA[Let him, then, be seated and say:]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I bear witness to Thy unity and Thy oneness, and that Thou art God, and that there is none other God beside Thee. Thou hast, verily, revealed Thy Cause, fulfilled Thy Covenant, and opened wide the door of Thy grace to all that dwell in heaven and on earth. Blessing and peace, salutation and glory, rest upon Thy loved ones, whom the changes and chances of the world have not deterred from turning unto Thee, and who have given their all, in the hope of obtaining that which is with Thee. Thou art, in truth, the Ever-Forgiving, the All-Bountiful.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Medium Obligatory Prayer, paragraph 6]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5111">
    <introtext><![CDATA[(If anyone choose to recite instead of the long verse these words: “God testifieth that there is none other God but Him, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting,” it would be sufficient. And likewise, it would suffice were he, while seated, to choose to recite these words: “I bear witness to Thy unity and Thy oneness, and that Thou art God, and that there is none other God beside Thee.”)]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[ ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Medium Obligatory Prayer, postscript]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>