<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Mankind" id="37">
  <quote id="794">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[My God, Whom I worship and adore! I bear witness unto Thy unity and Thy oneness, and acknowledge Thy gifts, both in the past and in the present. Thou art the All-Bountiful, the overflowing showers of Whose mercy have rained down upon high and low alike, and the splendors of Whose grace have been shed over both the obedient and the rebellious. <br/>
O God of mercy, before Whose door the quintessence of mercy hath bowed down, and round the sanctuary of Whose Cause loving-kindness, in its inmost spirit, hath circled, we beseech Thee, entreating Thine ancient grace, and seeking Thy present favor, that Thou mayest have mercy upon all who are the manifestations of the world of being, and deny them not the outpourings of Thy grace in Thy days. <br/>
All are but poor and needy, and Thou, verily, art the All-Possessing, the All-Subduing, the All-Powerful.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.99]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="795">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O Thou compassionate Lord, Thou Who art generous and able! We are servants of Thine sheltered beneath Thy providence. Cast Thy glance of favor upon us. Give light to our eyes, hearing to our ears, and understanding and love to our hearts. Render our souls joyous and happy through Thy glad tidings. O Lord! Point out to us the pathway of Thy kingdom and resuscitate all of us through the breaths of the Holy Spirit. Bestow upon us life everlasting and confer upon us never-ending honor. Unify mankind and illumine the world of humanity. May we all follow Thy pathway, long for Thy good pleasure and seek the mysteries of Thy kingdom. O God! Unite us and connect our hearts with Thy indissoluble bond. Verily, Thou art the Giver, Thou art the Kind One and Thou art the Almighty.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA['Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.100]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="796">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O Thou kind Lord! O Thou Who art generous and merciful! We are servants of Thy threshold and are gathered beneath the sheltering shadow of Thy divine unity. The sun of Thy mercy is shining upon all, and the clouds of Thy bounty shower upon all. Thy gifts encompass all, Thy loving providence sustains all, Thy protection overshadows all, and the glances of Thy favor are cast upon all. O Lord! Grant Thine infinite bestowals, and let the light of Thy guidance shine. Illumine the eyes, gladden the hearts with abiding joy. Confer a new spirit upon all people and bestow upon them eternal life. Unlock the gates of true understanding and let the light of faith shine resplendent. Gather all people beneath the shadow of Thy bounty and cause them to unite in harmony, so that they may become as the rays of one sun, as the waves of one ocean, and as the fruit of one tree. May they drink from the same fountain. May they be refreshed by the same breeze. May they receive illumination from the same source of light. Thou art the Giver, the Merciful, the Omnipotent.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA['Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.100-101]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="797">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O Thou kind Lord! Thou hast created all humanity from the same stock. Thou hast decreed that all shall belong to the same household. In Thy Holy Presence they are all Thy servants, and all mankind are sheltered beneath Thy Tabernacle; all have gathered together at Thy Table of Bounty; all are illumined through the light of Thy Providence. <br/>
O God! Thou art kind to all, Thou hast provided for all, dost shelter all, conferrest life upon all. Thou hast endowed each and all with talents and faculties, and all are submerged in the Ocean of Thy Mercy. <br/>
O Thou kind Lord! Unite all. Let the religions agree and make the nations one, so that they may see each other as one family and the whole earth as one home. May they all live together in perfect harmony. <br/>
O God! Raise aloft the banner of the oneness of mankind. <br/>
O God! Establish the Most Great Peace. <br/>
Cement Thou, O God, the hearts together. <br/>
O Thou kind Father, God! Gladden our hearts through the fragrance of Thy love. Brighten our eyes through the Light of Thy Guidance. Delight our ears with the melody of Thy Word, and shelter us all in the Stronghold of Thy Providence.
Thou art the Mighty and Powerful, Thou art the Forgiving and Thou art the One Who overlooketh the shortcomings of all mankind.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA['Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.101-102]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="798">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O God, O Thou Who hast cast Thy splendor over the luminous realities of men, shedding upon them the resplendent lights of knowledge and guidance, and hast chosen them out of all created things for this supernal grace, and hast caused them to encompass all things, to understand their inmost essence, and to disclose their mysteries, bringing them forth out of darkness into the visible world! "He verily showeth His special mercy to whomsoever He will." <br/>
O Lord, help Thou Thy loved ones to acquire knowledge and the sciences and arts, and to unravel the secrets that are treasured up in the inmost reality of all created beings. Make them to hear the hidden truths that are written and embedded in the heart of all that is. Make them to be ensigns of guidance amongst all creatures, and piercing rays of the mind shedding forth their light in this, the "first life." Make them to be leaders unto Thee, guides unto Thy path, runners urging men on to Thy Kingdom. <br/>
Thou verily art the Powerful, the Protector, the Potent, the Defender, the Mighty, the Most Generous.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA['Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.103]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>