<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Unity" id="163">
  <quote id="5168">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O my God! O my God! Unite the hearts of Thy servants, and reveal to them Thy great purpose. May they follow Thy commandments and abide in Thy law. Help them, O God, in their endeavor, and grant them strength to serve Thee. O God! Leave them not to themselves, but guide their steps by the light of Thy knowledge, and cheer their hearts by Thy love. Verily, Thou art their Helper and their Lord.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá’í Prayers, p. 204]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="5169">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O my God! O my God! Verily, I invoke Thee and supplicate before Thy threshold, asking Thee that all Thy mercies may descend upon these souls. Specialize them for Thy favor and Thy truth. <br/>
O Lord! Unite and bind together the hearts, join in accord all the souls, and exhilarate the spirits through the signs of Thy sanctity and oneness. O Lord! Make these faces radiant through the light of Thy oneness. Strengthen the loins of Thy servants in the service of Thy kingdom. <br/>
O Lord, Thou possessor of infinite mercy! O Lord of forgiveness and pardon! Forgive our sins, pardon our shortcomings, and cause us to turn to the kingdom of Thy clemency, invoking the kingdom of might and power, humble at Thy shrine and submissive before the glory of Thine evidences. <br/>
O Lord God! Make us as waves of the sea, as flowers of the garden, united, agreed through the bounties of Thy love. O Lord! Dilate the breasts through the signs of Thy oneness, and make all mankind as stars shining from the same height of glory, as perfect fruits growing upon Thy tree of life. <br/>
Verily, Thou art the Almighty, the Self-Subsistent, the Giver, the Forgiving, the Pardoner, the Omniscient, the One Creator. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá’í Prayers, p. 204-205]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>