<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Prayers" id="11">
  <quote id="298">
	<id>298</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[I bear witness, O my God, <br/> that Thou hast created me to know Thee and to worship Thee. <br/> I testify, at this moment, to my powerlessness and to Thy might, to my poverty and to Thy wealth. <br/>There is none other God but Thee, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="299">
	<id>299</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Blessed is the spot, and the house, and the place, and the city, and the heart, and the mountain, and the refuge, and the cave, and the valley, and the land, and the sea, and the island, and the meadow where mention of God hath been made, and His praise glorified.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="300">
	<id>300</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[My God, my Adored One, my King, my Desire! What tongue can voice my thanks to Thee? I was heedless, Thou didst awaken me. I had turned back from Thee, Thou didst graciously aid me to turn towards Thee. I was as one dead, Thou didst quicken me with the water of life. I was withered, Thou didst revive me with the heavenly stream of Thine utterance which hath flowed forth from the Pen of the All-Merciful.<br/> O Divine Providence! All existence is begotten by Thy bounty; deprive it not of the waters of Thy generosity, neither do Thou withhold it from the ocean of Thy mercy. I beseech Thee to aid and assist me at all times and under all conditions, and seek from the heaven of Thy grace Thine ancient favor. Thou art, in truth, the Lord of bounty, and the Sovereign of the kingdom of eternity.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="301">
	<id>301</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[ Lord! Pitiful are we, grant us Thy favor; poor, bestow upon us a share from the ocean of Thy wealth; needy, do Thou satisfy us; abased, give us Thy glory. The fowls of the air and the beasts of the field receive their meat each day from Thee, and all beings partake of Thy care and loving-kindness.<br/> Deprive not this feeble one of Thy wondrous grace and vouchsafe by Thy might unto this helpless soul Thy bounty.<br/> Give us our daily bread, and grant Thine increase in the necessities of life, that we may be dependent on none other but Thee, may commune wholly with Thee, may walk in Thy ways and declare Thy mysteries. Thou art the Almighty and the Loving and the Provider of all mankind. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="302">
	<id>302</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Say: God sufficeth all things above all things, and nothing in the heavens or in the earth but God sufficeth. Verily, He is in Himself the Knower, the Sustainer, the Omnipotent.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="303">
	<id>303</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[I adjure Thee by Thy might, O my God! Let no harm beset me in times of tests, and in moments of heedlessness guide my steps aright through Thine inspiration. Thou art God, potent art Thou to do what Thou desirest. No one can withstand Thy Will or thwart Thy Purpose.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="304">
	<id>304</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[ O God! Educate these children. These children are the plants of Thine orchard, the flowers of Thy meadow, the roses of Thy garden. Let Thy rain fall upon them; let the Sun of Reality shine upon them with Thy love. Let Thy breeze refresh them in order that they may be trained, grow and develop, and appear in the utmost beauty. Thou art the Giver. Thou art the Compassionate.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA['Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="305">
	<id>305</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[I beg Thee to forgive me, O my Lord, for every mention but the mention of Thee, and for every praise but the praise of Thee, and for every delight but delight in Thy nearness, and for every pleasure but the pleasure of communion with Thee, and for every joy but the joy of Thy love and of Thy good-pleasure, and for all things pertaining unto me which bear no relationship unto Thee, O Thou Who art the Lord of lords, He Who provideth the means and unlocketh the doors.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="306">
	<id>306</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Thy name is my healing, O my God, and remembrance of Thee is my remedy. Nearness to Thee is my hope, and love for Thee is my companion. Thy mercy to me is my healing and my succor in both this world and the world to come. Thou, verily, art the All-Bountiful, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="307">
	<id>307</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[I have wakened in Thy shelter, O my God, and it becometh him that seeketh that shelter to abide within the Sanctuary of Thy protection and the Stronghold of Thy defense. Illumine my inner being, O my Lord, with the splendors of the Dayspring of Thy Revelation, even as Thou didst illumine my outer being with the morning light of Thy favor.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="308">
	<id>308</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Create in me a pure heart, O my God, and renew a tranquil conscience within me, O my Hope! Through the spirit of power confirm Thou me in Thy Cause, O my Best-Beloved, and by the light of Thy glory reveal unto me Thy path, O Thou the Goal of my desire! Through the power of Thy transcendent might lift me up unto the heaven of Thy holiness, O Source of my being, and by the breezes of Thine eternity gladden me, O Thou Who art my God! Let Thine everlasting melodies breathe tranquillity on me, O my Companion, and let the riches of Thine ancient countenance deliver me from all except Thee, O my Master, and let the tidings of the revelation of Thine incorruptible Essence bring me joy, O Thou Who art the most manifest of the manifest and the most hidden of the hidden!]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="309">
	<id>309</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O my Lord! Make Thy beauty to be my food, and Thy presence my drink, and Thy pleasure my hope, and praise of Thee my action, and remembrance of Thee my companion, and the power of Thy sovereignty my succorer, and Thy habitation my home, and my dwelling-place the seat Thou hast sanctified from the limitations imposed upon them who are shut out as by a veil from Thee.<br/> Thou art, verily, the Almighty, the All-Glorious, the Most Powerful.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="310">
	<id>310</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O God! Refresh and gladden my spirit. Purify my heart. Illumine my powers. I lay all my affairs in Thy hand. Thou art my Guide and my Refuge. I will no longer be sorrowful and grieved; I will be a happy and joyful being. O God! I will no longer be full of anxiety, nor will I let trouble harass me. I will not dwell on the unpleasant things of life.<br/> O God! Thou art more friend to me than I am to myself. I dedicate myself to Thee, O Lord.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="311">
	<id>311</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O Lord my God! Assist Thy loved ones to be firm in Thy Faith, to walk in Thy ways, to be steadfast in Thy Cause. Give them Thy grace to withstand the onslaught of self and passion, to follow the light of divine guidance. Thou art the Powerful, the Gracious, the Self-Subsisting, the Bestower, the Compassionate, the Almighty, the All-Bountiful.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="312">
	<id>312</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O my God! O my God! Unite the hearts of Thy servants, and reveal to them Thy great purpose. May they follow Thy commandments and abide in Thy law. Help them, O God, in their endeavor, and grant them strength to serve Thee. O God! Leave them not to themselves, but guide their steps by the light of Thy knowledge, and cheer their hearts by Thy love. Verily, Thou art their Helper and their Lord.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>