<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Morning" id="40">
  <quote id="811">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O my God and my Master! I am Thy servant and the son of Thy servant. I have risen from my couch at this dawntide when the Daystar of Thy oneness hath shone forth from the Dayspring of Thy will, and hath shed its radiance upon the whole world, according to what had been ordained in the Books of Thy Decree. <br/>
Praise be unto Thee, O my God, that we have wakened to the splendors of the light of Thy knowledge. Send down, then, upon us, O my Lord, what will enable us to dispense with anyone but Thee, and will rid us of all attachment to aught except Thyself. Write down, moreover, for me, and for such as are dear to me, and for my kindred, man and woman alike, the good of this world and the world to come. Keep us safe, then, through Thine unfailing protection, O Thou the Beloved of the entire creation and the Desire of the whole universe, from them whom Thou hast made to be the manifestations of the Evil Whisperer, who whisper in men's breasts. Potent art Thou to do Thy pleasure. Thou art, verily, the Almighty, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting. <br/>
Bless Thou, O Lord my God, Him Whom Thou hast set over Thy most excellent Titles, and through Whom Thou hast divided between the godly and the wicked, and graciously aid us to do what Thou lovest and desirest. Bless Thou, moreover, O my God, them Who are Thy Words and Thy Letters, and them who have set their faces towards Thee, and turned unto Thy face, and hearkened to Thy Call. <br/>
Thou art, truly, the Lord and King of all men, and art potent over all things. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.116-117]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="812">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I have wakened in Thy shelter, O my God, and it becometh him that seeketh that shelter to abide within the Sanctuary of Thy protection and the Stronghold of Thy defense. Illumine my inner being, O my Lord, with the splendors of the Dayspring of Thy Revelation, even as Thou didst illumine my outer being with the morning light of Thy favor.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.117]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="813">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I have risen this morning by Thy grace, O my God, and left my home trusting wholly in Thee, and committing myself to Thy care. Send down, then, upon me, out of the heaven of Thy mercy, a blessing from Thy side, and enable me to return home in safety even as Thou didst enable me to set out under Thy protection with my thoughts fixed steadfastly upon Thee. <br/>
There is none other God but Thee, the One, the Incomparable, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.118]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="814">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[I give praise to Thee, O my God, that Thou hast awakened me out of my sleep, and brought me forth after my disappearance, and raised me up from my slumber. I have wakened this morning with my face set toward the splendors of the Daystar of Thy Revelation, through Which the heavens of Thy power and Thy majesty have been illumined, acknowledging Thy signs, believing in Thy Book, and holding fast unto Thy Cord. <br/>
I beseech Thee, by the potency of Thy will and the compelling power of Thy purpose, to make of what Thou didst reveal unto me in my sleep the surest foundation for the mansions of Thy love that are within the hearts of Thy loved ones, and the best instrument for the revelation of the tokens of Thy grace and Thy loving-kindness.
Do Thou ordain for me through Thy most exalted Pen, O my Lord, the good of this world and of the next. I testify that within Thy grasp are held the reins of all things. Thou changest them as Thou pleasest. No God is there save Thee, the Strong, the Faithful. <br/>
Thou art He Who changeth through His bidding abasement into glory, and weakness into strength, and powerlessness into might, and fear into calm, and doubt into certainty. No God is there but Thee, the Mighty, the Beneficent. <br/>
Thou disappointest no one who hath sought Thee, nor dost Thou keep back from Thee anyone who hath desired Thee. Ordain Thou for me what becometh the heaven of Thy generosity, and the ocean of Thy bounty. Thou art, verily, the Almighty, the Most Powerful.
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.118-119]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>