<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Protection" id="42">
  <quote id="821">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Praise be to Thee, O Lord my God! Thou seest and knowest that I have called upon Thy servants to turn nowhere except in the direction of Thy bestowals, and have bidden them observe naught save the things Thou didst prescribe in Thy Perspicuous Book, the Book which hath been sent down according to Thine inscrutable decree and irrevocable purpose. <br/>
I can utter no word, O my God, unless I be permitted by Thee, and can move in no direction until I obtain Thy sanction. It is Thou, O my God, Who hast called me into being through the power of Thy might, and hast endued me with Thy grace to manifest Thy Cause. Wherefore I have been subjected to such adversities that my tongue hath been hindered from extolling Thee and from magnifying Thy glory. <br/>
All praise be to Thee, O my God, for the things Thou didst ordain for me through Thy decree and by the power of Thy sovereignty. I beseech Thee that Thou wilt fortify both myself and them that love me in our love for Thee, and wilt keep us firm in Thy Cause. I swear by Thy might! O my God! Thy servant's shame is to be shut out as by a veil from Thee, and his glory is to know Thee. Armed with the power of Thy name nothing can ever hurt me, and with Thy love in my heart all the world's afflictions can in no wise alarm me. <br/>
Send down, therefore, O my Lord, upon me and upon my loved ones that which will protect us from the mischief of those that have repudiated Thy truth and disbelieved in Thy signs. <br/>
Thou art, verily, the All-Glorious, the Most Bountiful.
—Bahá'u'lláh ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.128-129]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="822">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Praised be Thou, O Lord my God! This is Thy servant who hath quaffed from the hands of Thy grace the wine of Thy tender mercy, and tasted of the savor of Thy love in Thy days. I beseech Thee, by the embodiments of Thy names whom no grief can hinder from rejoicing in Thy love or from gazing on Thy face, and whom all the hosts of the heedless are powerless to cause to turn aside from the path of Thy pleasure, to supply him with the good things Thou dost possess, and to raise him up to such heights that he will regard the world even as a shadow that vanisheth swifter than the twinkling of an eye. <br/>
Keep him safe also, O my God, by the power of Thine immeasurable majesty, from all that Thou abhorrest. Thou art, verily, his Lord and the Lord of all worlds.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.129-130]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="823">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Lauded be Thy name, O Lord my God! I entreat Thee by Thy Name through which the Hour hath struck, and the Resurrection came to pass, and fear and trembling seized all that are in heaven and all that are on earth, to rain down, out of the heaven of Thy mercy and the clouds of Thy tender compassion, what will gladden the hearts of Thy servants, who have turned towards Thee and helped Thy Cause. <br/>
Keep safe Thy servants and Thy handmaidens, O my Lord, from the darts of idle fancy and vain imaginings, and give them from the hands of Thy grace a draught of the soft-flowing waters of Thy knowledge. <br/>
Thou, truly, art the Almighty, the Most Exalted, the Ever-Forgiving, the Most Generous. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.130-131]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="824">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O God, my God! I have set out from my home, holding fast unto the cord of Thy love, and I have committed myself wholly to Thy care and Thy protection. I entreat Thee by Thy power through which Thou didst protect Thy loved ones from the wayward and the perverse, and from every contumacious oppressor, and every wicked doer who hath strayed far from Thee, to keep me safe by Thy bounty and Thy grace. Enable me, then, to return to my home by Thy power and Thy might. Thou art, truly, the Almighty, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá'u'lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.131]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="825">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Ordain for me, O my Lord, and for those who believe in Thee that which is deemed best for us in Thine estimation, as set forth in the Mother Book, for within the grasp of Thy hand Thou holdest the determined measures of all things. <br/>
Thy goodly gifts are unceasingly showered upon such as cherish Thy love, and the wondrous tokens of Thy heavenly bounties are amply bestowed on those who recognize Thy divine Unity. We commit unto Thy care whatsoever Thou hast destined for us, and implore Thee to grant us all the good that Thy knowledge embraceth. <br/>
Protect me, O my Lord, from every evil that Thine omniscience perceiveth, inasmuch as there is no power nor strength but in Thee, no triumph is forthcoming save from Thy presence, and it is Thine alone to command. Whatever God hath willed hath been, and that which He hath not willed shall not be. <br/>
There is no power nor strength except in God, the Most Exalted, the Most Mighty. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.131-132]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="826">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[Glory be to Thee, O God! Thou art the God Who hath existed before all things, Who will exist after all things and will last beyond all things. Thou art the God Who knoweth all things, and is supreme over all things. Thou art the God Who dealeth mercifully with all things, Who judgeth between all things and Whose vision embraceth all things. Thou art God my Lord, Thou art aware of my position, Thou dost witness my inner and outer being. <br/>
Grant Thy forgiveness unto me and unto the believers who responded to Thy Call. Be Thou my sufficing helper against the mischief of whosoever may desire to inflict sorrow upon me or wish me ill. Verily, Thou art the Lord of all created things. Thou dost suffice everyone, while no one can be self-sufficient without Thee.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.132-133]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="827">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[In the Name of God, the Lord of overpowering majesty, the All-Compelling. <br/>
Hallowed be the Lord in Whose hand is the source of dominion. He createth whatsoever He willeth by His Word of command "Be," and it is. His hath been the power of authority heretofore, and it shall remain His hereafter. He maketh victorious whomsoever He pleaseth, through the potency of His behest. He is in truth the Powerful, the Almighty. Unto Him pertaineth all glory and majesty in the kingdoms of Revelation and Creation and whatever lieth between them. Verily, He is the Potent, the All-Glorious. From everlasting He hath been the Source of indomitable strength and shall remain so unto everlasting. He is indeed the Lord of might and power. All the kingdoms of heaven and earth and whatever is between them are God's, and His power is supreme over all things. All the treasures of earth and heaven and everything between them are His, and His protection extendeth over all things. He is the Creator of the heavens and the earth and whatever lieth between them, and He truly is a witness over all things. He is the Lord of Reckoning for all that dwell in the heavens and on earth and whatever lieth between them, and truly God is swift to reckon. He setteth the measure assigned to all who are in the heavens and the earth and whatever is between them. Verily, He is the Supreme Protector. He holdeth in His grasp the keys of heaven and earth and of everything between them. At His Own pleasure doth He bestow gifts, through the power of His command. Indeed His grace encompasseth all, and He is the All-Knowing. <br/>
Say: God sufficeth unto me; He is the One Who holdeth in His grasp the kingdom of all things. Through the power of His hosts of heaven and earth and whatever lieth between them, He protecteth whomsoever among His servants He willeth. God, in truth, keepeth watch over all things. <br/>
Immeasurably exalted art Thou, O Lord! Protect us from what lieth in front of us and behind us, above our heads, on our right, on our left, below our feet and every other side to which we are exposed. Verily, Thy protection over all things is unfailing.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[The Báb]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.133-135]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="828">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O God, my God! Shield Thy trusted servants from the evils of self and passion, protect them with the watchful eye of Thy loving-kindness from all rancor, hate and envy, shelter them in the impregnable stronghold of Thy care and, safe from the darts of doubtfulness, make them the manifestations of Thy glorious signs, illumine their faces with the effulgent rays shed from the Dayspring of Thy divine unity, gladden their hearts with the verses revealed from Thy holy kingdom, strengthen their loins by Thine all-swaying power that cometh from Thy realm of glory. Thou art the All-Bountiful, the Protector, the Almighty, the Gracious.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA['Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.135-136]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
    <quote id="829">
    <introtext><![CDATA[]]></introtext>
	<text><![CDATA[O my Lord! Thou knowest that the people are encircled with pain and calamities and are environed with hardships and trouble. Every trial doth attack man and every dire adversity doth assail him like unto the assault of a serpent. There is no shelter and asylum for him except under the wing of Thy protection, preservation, guard and custody. <br/>
O Thou the Merciful One! O my Lord! Make Thy protection my armor, Thy preservation my shield, humbleness before the door of Thy oneness my guard, and Thy custody and defense my fortress and my abode. Preserve me from the suggestions of self and desire, and guard me from every sickness, trial, difficulty and ordeal. <br/>
Verily, Thou art the Protector, the Guardian, the Preserver, the Sufficer, and verily, Thou art the Merciful of the Most Merciful. ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA['Abdu'l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p.136]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>