<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Ruhi Book 7" id="8">
  <quote id="223">
	<id>223</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O My servants! Were ye to discover the hidden, the shoreless oceans of My incorruptible wealth, ye would, of a certainty, esteem as nothing the world, nay, the entire creation.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 323]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="224">
	<id>224</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[He is the Compassionate, the All-Bountiful! O God, my God! Thou seest me, Thou knowest me; Thou art my Haven and my Refuge. None have I sought nor any will I seek save Thee; no path have I trodden nor any will I tread but the path of Thy love. In the darksome night of despair, my eye turneth expectant and full of hope to the morn of Thy boundless favour and at the hour of dawn my drooping soul is refreshed and strengthened in remembrance of Thy beauty and perfection. He whom the grace of Thy mercy aideth, though he be but a drop, shall become the boundless ocean, and the merest atom which the outpouring of Thy loving-kindness assisteth, shall shine even as the radiant star. Shelter under Thy protection, O Thou Spirit of purity, Thou Who art the All-Bountiful Provider, this enthralled, enkindled servant of Thine. Aid him in this world of being to remain steadfast and firm in Thy love and grant that this broken-winged bird attain a refuge and shelter in Thy divine nest that abideth upon the celestial tree.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í Prayers, p. 30]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="225">
	<id>225</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Thus I exhort each of you, realizing its power and beauty, to sacrifice all your thoughts, words and actions to bring the knowledge of the Love of God into every heart.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Paris Talks, p. 81]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="226">
	<id>226</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[… ye must in this matter -- that is, the serving of humankind -- lay down your very lives, and as ye yield yourselves, rejoice.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 72]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="227">
	<id>227</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[If only thou couldst know what a high station is destined for those souls who are severed from the world, are powerfully attracted to the Faith, and are teaching, under the sheltering shadow of Bahá'u'lláh! How thou wouldst rejoice, how thou wouldst, in exultation and rapture, spread thy wings and soar heavenward -- for being a follower of such a way, and a traveller toward such a Kingdom.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 100
]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="228">
	<id>228</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Hold ye fast to the hem of God's garment, and direct all your efforts toward furthering His Covenant, and burning ever more brightly with the fire of His love, that your hearts may leap for joy in the breathings of servitude which well out from the breast of 'Abdu'l-Bahá.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 85]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="229">
	<id>229</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Let us put aside all thoughts of self; let us close our eyes to all on earth, let us neither make known our sufferings nor complain of our wrongs. Rather let us become oblivious of our own selves, and drinking down the wine of heavenly grace, let us cry out our joy, and lose ourselves in the beauty of the All-Glorious.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 236]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="230">
	<id>230</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Ye are the angels, if your feet be firm, your spirits rejoiced, your secret thoughts pure, your eyes consoled, your ears opened, your breasts dilated with joy, and your souls gladdened, and if you arise to assist the Covenant, to resist dissension and to be attracted to the Effulgence!]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá'í World Faith, p. 359]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="231">
	<id>231</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[At all times do I speak of you and call you to mind. I pray unto the Lord, and with tears I implore Him to rain down all these blessings upon you, and gladden your hearts, and make blissful your souls, and grant you exceeding joy and heavenly delights....]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 37]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="232">
	<id>232</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[My only joy in this swiftly-passing world was to tread the stony path of God and to endure hard tests and all material griefs. For  otherwise, this earthly life would prove barren and vain, and better would be death. The tree of being would produce no fruit; the sown field of this existence would yield no harvest. Thus it is my hope that once again some circumstance will make my cup of anguish to brim over, and that beauteous Love, that Slayer of souls, will dazzle the beholders again. Then will this heart be blissful, this soul be blessed.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 226]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="233">
	<id>233</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Then rose the Sun of Truth and the splendours of the Kingdom were shed over east and west. Those who had eyes to see rejoiced at the glad tidings and cried out: 'O blessed, blessed are we!', and they witnessed the inner reality of all things, and uncovered the mysteries of the Kingdom. Delivered then from their fancies and their doubts, they beheld the light of truth, and so exhilarated did they become from draining the chalice of God's love, that they utterly forgot the world and their own selves. Dancing for joy they hastened to the place of their own martyrdom and there, where men die for love, they flung away their heads and hearts.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu'l-Bahá, p. 33]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="234">
	<id>234</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O God, O Thou Who hast cast Thy splendour over the luminous realities of men, shedding upon them the resplendent lights of knowledge and guidance, and hast chosen them out of all created things for this supernal grace, and hast caused them to encompass all things, to understand their inmost essence, and to disclose their mysteries, bringing them forth out of darkness into the visible world! "He verily showeth His special mercy to whomsoever He will. O Lord, help Thou Thy loved ones to acquire knowledge and the sciences and arts, and to unravel the secrets that are treasured up in the inmost reality of all created beings. Make them to hear the hidden truths that are written and embedded in the heart of all that is. Make them to be ensigns of guidance amongst all creatures, and piercing rays of the mind shedding forth their light in this, the "first life". Make them to be leaders unto Thee, guides unto Thy path, runners urging men on to Thy Kingdom. Thou verily art the Powerful, the Protector, the Potent, the Defender, the Mighty, the Most Generous.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[`Abdu'l-Baha]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[ The Compilation of Compilations vol. I, p. 251]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="235">
	<id>235</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Apart from these provisions Bahá'u'lláh exhorts His followers to consort, with amity and concord and without discrimination, with  the adherents of all religions; warns them to guard against fanaticism, sedition, pride, dispute and contention; inculcates upon them immaculate cleanliness, strict truthfulness, spotless chastity, trustworthiness; hospitality, fidelity, courtesy, forbearance, justice and fairness; counsels them to be "even as the fingers of one hand and the limbs of one body"; calls upon them to arise and serve His Cause; and assures them of His undoubted aid.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Shoghi Effendi]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[God Passes By, p. 214]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>