<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><quotes>
<section name="Ruhi Book 6" id="7">
  <quote id="204">
	<id>204</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O thou lamp who art enkindled with the fire of the Love of God! Verily, I read thy recent letter which showed thy strong love, thy being ablaze with the fire of the love of thy Lord, the Mighty, the Praised, and the penetration of the Spirit of Truth in thy limbs, nerves, veins, arteries, bones, blood and flesh, until it hath taken the reins of power from thy hands and moveth thee as it willeth, causeth thee to speak in what it willeth and attracteth thee as it willeth. This is becoming of whatever heart is replenished with the spirit of the love of God. Thou shalt surely behold wondrous traces and shalt discover the signs of thy Mighty Lord.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Tablets of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá vol 3, pp. 716-717 (Book 6, p. 11)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="205">
	<id>205</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Say: To assist Me is to teach My Cause. This is a theme with which whole Tablets are laden. This is the changeless commandment of God, eternal in the past, eternal in the future.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[ Tablets of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 196, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="206">
	<id>206</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Be not dismayed, O peoples of the world, when the day star of My beauty is set, and the heaven of My tabernacle is concealed from your eyes. Arise to further My Cause, and to exalt My Word amongst men. We are with you at all times, and shall strengthen you through the power of truth.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[ The Kitáb-i-Aqdas, p. 34, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="207">
	<id>207</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[The Pen of the Most High hath decreed and imposed upon every one the obligation to teach this Cause.... God will, no doubt, inspire whosoever detacheth himself from all else but Him, and will cause the pure waters of wisdom and utterance to gush out and flow copiously from his heart.    ]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 314, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="208">
	<id>208</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[God hath prescribed unto every one the duty of teaching His Cause. Whoever ariseth to discharge this duty, must needs, ere he proclaimeth His Message, adorn himself with the ornament of an upright and praiseworthy character, so that his words may attract the hearts of such as are receptive to his call.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 335, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="209">
	<id>209</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O ye beloved of God! Repose not yourselves on your couches, nay bestir yourselves as soon as ye recognize your Lord, the Creator, and hear of the things which have befallen Him, and hasten to His assistance. Unloose your tongues, and proclaim unceasingly His Cause. This shall be better for you than all the treasures of the past and of the future, if ye be of them that comprehend this truth.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 330, (Book 6 p. 15)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="210">
	<id>210</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[If one teaches one whom he loves because of his love for him, then he will not teach one whom he loves not; and that is not of God.  If one teaches in order to derive the promised benefit to himself, this too is not from God.   If he teaches because of God's Will that God may be known -- and for that reason only -- he will receive knowledge and wisdom, and his words will have effect -- being made powerful by the Holy Spirit -- and will take root in the souls of those who are in the right condition to receive them.  In such a case the benefit to the teacher in growth is as ninety percent compared to the ten percent of gain to the hearer, because he becomes like a tree bearing fruit through the power of God.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[cited in Star of the West, vol III, no. 19 (2 March 1913) p. 1, (Book 6 p. 18)
]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="211">
	<id>211</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[This is the day in which to speak. It is incumbent upon the people of Baha to strive, with the utmost patience and forbearance, to guide the peoples of the world to the Most Great Horizon. Every body calleth aloud for a soul. Heavenly souls must needs quicken, with the breath of the Word of God, the dead bodies with a fresh spirit.     
]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[cited in The Advent of Divine Justice, pp. 82-83, (Book 6 p. 28)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="212">
	<id>212</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O thou son of the Kingdom! All things are beneficial if joined with the love of God; and without His love all things are harmful, and act as a veil between man and the Lord of the Kingdom. When His love is there, every bitterness turneth sweet, and every bounty rendereth a wholesome pleasure. For example, a melody, sweet to the ear, bringeth the very spirit of life to a heart in love with God, yet staineth with lust a soul engrossed in sensual desires. And every branch of learning, conjoined with the love of God, is approved and worthy of praise; but bereft of His love, learning is barren -- indeed, it bringeth on madness. Every kind of knowledge, every science, is as a tree: if the fruit of it be the love of God, then is it a blessed tree, but if not, that tree is but dried-up wood, and shall only feed the fire.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, p. 190, (Book 6 p. 34)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="213">
	<id>213</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[By the righteousness of God! Whoso openeth his lips in this Day and maketh mention of the name of his Lord, the hosts of Divine inspiration shall descend upon him from the heaven of My name, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise. On him shall also descend the Concourse on high, each bearing aloft a chalice of pure light. Thus hath it been foreordained in the realm of God's Revelation, by the behest of Him Who is the All-Glorious, the Most Powerful.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 280, (Book 6 p. 34)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="214">
	<id>214</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[They that have forsaken their country for the purpose of teaching Our Cause -- these shall the Faithful Spirit strengthen through its power. A company of Our chosen angels shall go forth with them, as bidden by Him Who is the Almighty, the All-Wise. How great the blessedness that awaiteth him that hath attained the honor of serving the Almighty!]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[ Gleanings from the Writings of Bahá’u’lláh, p. 334, (Book 6 pp. 34/35)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="215">
	<id>215</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[He, verily, will aid everyone that aideth Him, and will remember everyone that remembereth Him. To this beareth witness this Tablet that hath shed the splendor of the loving-kindness of your Lord, the All-Glorious, the All-Compelling.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[cited in The Advent of Divine Justice, p. 76, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="216">
	<id>216</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Say: Beware, O people of Baha, lest the strong ones of the earth rob you of your strength, or they who rule the world fill you with fear. Put your trust in God, and commit your affairs to His keeping. He, verily, will, through the power of truth, render you victorious, and He, verily, is powerful to do what He willeth, and in His grasp are the reins of omnipotent might.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[cited in The Advent of Divine Justice p. 82, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="217">
	<id>217</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[By God besides Whom is none other God! Should any one arise for the triumph of our Cause, him will God render victorious though tens of thousands of enemies be leagued against him. And if his love for Me wax stronger, God will establish his ascendancy over all the powers of earth and heaven. Thus have We breathed the spirit of power into all regions.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Bahá’u’lláh]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[cited in The World Order of Bahá’u’lláh: Selected Letters, p.106, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="218">
	<id>218</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[He will come to your aid with invisible hosts, and support you with armies of inspiration from the Concourse above; He will send unto you sweet perfumes from the highest Paradise, and waft over you the pure breathings that blow from the rose gardens of the Company on high. He will breathe into your hearts the spirit of life, cause you to enter the Ark of salvation, and reveal unto you His clear tokens and signs. Verily is this abounding grace. Verily is this the victory that none can deny.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, no. 157, p. 196, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="219">
	<id>219</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[O ye servants of the Sacred Threshold! The triumphant hosts of the Celestial Concourse, arrayed and marshaled in the Realms above, stand ready and expectant to assist and assure victory to that valiant horseman who with confidence spurs on his charger into the arena of service. Well is it with that fearless warrior, who armed with the power of true Knowledge, hastens unto the field, disperses the armies of ignorance, and scatters the hosts of error, who holds aloft the Standard of Divine Guidance, and sounds the Clarion of Victory. By the righteousness of the Lord! He hath achieved a glorious triumph and obtained the true victory.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, no. 208, pp. 276-77, (Book 6 p. 35)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="220">
	<id>220</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[Let us too bear in mind the example which our beloved Master has clearly set before us. Wise and tactful in His approach, wakeful and attentive in His early intercourse, broad and liberal in all His public utterances, cautious and gradual in the unfolding of the essential verities of the Cause, passionate in His appeal yet sober in argument, confident in tone, unswerving in conviction, dignified in His manners -- such were the distinguishing features of our Beloved's noble presentation of the Cause of Bahá’u’lláh.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Shoghi Effendi]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Bahá’í Administration:  Selected Messages, pp. 69-70, (Book 6 p. 70)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="221">
	<id>221</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[As for you, O ye lovers of God, make firm your steps in His Cause, with such resolve that ye shall not be shaken though the direst of calamities assail the world. By nothing, under no conditions, be ye perturbed. Be ye anchored fast as the high mountains, be stars that dawn over the horizon of life, be bright lamps in the gatherings of unity, be souls humble and lowly in the presence of the friends, be innocent in heart. Be ye symbols of guidance and lights of godliness, severed from the world, clinging to the handhold that is sure and strong, spreading abroad the spirit of life, riding the Ark of salvation. Be ye daysprings of generosity, dawning-points of the mysteries of existence, sites where inspiration alighteth, rising-places of splendours, souls that are sustained by the Holy Spirit, enamoured of the Lord, detached from all save Him, holy above the characteristics of humankind, clothed in the attributes of the angels of heaven, that ye may win for yourselves the highest bestowal of all, in this new time, this wondrous age.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[‘Abdu’l-Bahá]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[Selections from the Writings of ‘Abdu’l-Bahá, no. 199, p. 253, (Book 6 p. 73)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
    <quote id="222">
	<id>222</id> 
	<text><![CDATA[The opportunities which the turmoil of the present age presents, with all the sorrows which it evokes, the fears which it excites, the disillusionment which it produces, the perplexities which it creates, the indignation which it arouses, the revolt which it provokes, the grievances it engenders, the spirit of restless search which it awakens, must, in like manner, be exploited for the purpose of spreading far and wide, the knowledge of the redemptive power of the Faith of Bahá’u’lláh, and for enlisting fresh recruits in the ever-swelling army of His followers. So precious an opportunity, so rare a conjunction of favorable circumstances, may never again recur.]]></text>
 	<author><![CDATA[Shoghi Effendi]]></author>
  	<reference><![CDATA[The Advent of Divine Justice, p. 48, (Book 6 p. 87)]]></reference>
    <language>en</language>
  </quote>
  </section>
</quotes>